al al
al al
[Music]
[Música]
Oh
Oh
ha
ha
[Music]
[Música]
H
H
ha
ha
[Music]
[Música]
Good night
Buenas noches
family It's nice not to come here at
familia Qué bien no venir por aquí por
night it's been a while since I came
la noche hacía tiempo que no venía Yo
here at night Not alone I mean
por aquí por la noche Solo no O sea
whenever I come I come in like a
siempre que vengo vengo con como con
hurry always eh I mean in a hurry I always
prisa siempre eh o sea con prisa Siempre
go the truth is I have to
voy la verdad es que os tengo que
admit that I've run from the gym I've
reconocer que del gimnasio he corrido me
sat here I've eaten here okay And
he sentado aquí he comido aquí vale Y
here I am with you guys it's just that if we didn't
aquí estoy con ustedes es que si no
start at 11 Then later
empezábamos a las 11 Entonces ya luego
calm down Well then I'm going to go to the
tranquilo Bueno luego me voy a ir a la
salsería for a while and anyway well anyway
salsería un rato y en fin bueno en fin
crazy okay I'm going to ask you something I'm
locura vale os voy a pedir una cosa os
going to ask you something
voy a pedir una cosa
okay Because I know that you're not going to let me down
okay Que yo sé que no me Vais a fallar
I know that
Yo sé que la
gentlemen we have uploaded to the
señoreros hemos subido a al Canal
main Channel the chat with Pedro García
principal la charla con Pedro García
guado because I loved it and we have
guado porque me encantó y la hemos
uploaded to the main Channel well edited it
subido al Canal principal bien editad it
and all those things okay I'm going to let you know on
y todas esas cosas vale voy a avisar en
WhatsApp what you want Indian wait now I'll
WhatsApp qué quies indio espérate ahora
read you
te leo
family the route of the cod  start okay
familia la ruta del bacalao empieza vale
we're on telesalseo come over here and
estamos en telesalseo veniros para acá y
then we'll go to the salseria and
ya luego nos vamos para la salsería y
well the night
bueno la noche
young I have seemed young and everything eh there
joven he parecido joven y todo eh ahí
eh I have seemed young and everything there eh the
eh he parecido joven y todo ahí eh la
house Thank you very much handsome how
casito Muchas gracias guapo qué tal
are you
estás
I have seen it to see to see I know that many
Yo la he visto a ver a ver Sé que mucha
people have seen it and yesterday I know but
gente la ha visto y ayer lo sé pero
well you can stop by the
bueno os podéis pasar por el canal
main channel leave a like put a
principal dejáis un like ponéis un
comment No because the more
comentario No porque cuanto Cuanto más
you enter The more you enter and give it a
entréis Cuanto más entréis y le deis
like and all that stuff the more it gets
like y todo el rollo ese más se
positioned yes it's true that man if
posiciona sí que es verdad que hombre si
people are only going to enter To
la gente solamente va a entrar Para
give it that I don't know if that
darle eso no sé si eso de la retención
audience retention can screw it up I don't know the
de audiencia puede joderlo No lo sé la
truth I don't know the truth
verdad No lo sé la verdad
e But well if you support it I
e Pero bueno si lo apoyáis os lo
appreciate it I know that
agradezco Yo sé que la
gentlemen well we are going to cover the topics
señoreros pues vamos a tratar los temas
that I had prepared okay To be
que yo tenía preparados okay Para estar
here with you but it's that of course
aquí con ustedes pero es que claro es
something has happened something powerful has happened
que ha pasado algo es que ha pasado algo
eh that t-shirt that you're wearing ji I
eh esa camiseta que llevas ji se la he
bought it for my grandson the same one
comprado a mi nieto la misma pues
Josefina Maybe I am your grandson and you haven't
Josefina A lo mejor soy tu nieto y no te
realized it you have
has dado cuenta lo has
rated let's see I think the shirt I think
valorado a ver creo que la camiseta creo
is from the beach eh I mean I think it's like
que es de la playa eh o sea creo que es
from Some beach like the street
en plan de de Alguna playa en plan los
vendors on the
vendedores ambulantes de la
beach I think I think it was from the beach
playa Creo que creo que era de la playa
eh if I'm honest let's say if I'm
eh si te digo la verdad vamos si te digo
honest I think it was from the
la verdad creo que era de la
beach but oh well
playa pero bueno
But oh
Pero
well I don't usually like to wear a
bueno no me suele gustar mucho utilizar
tank top but this one Yes and I
camiseta de tiranta pero esta Sí y me
bought another one at the
compré otra en el parque de la
Warner park the last time I was in
Warner la última vez que estuve en
Madrid tesa Thanks sweetheart a
Madrid tesa Gracias corazón un
kiss I bought one at Warner that is
beso me compré una en la Warner que
also a tank top I mean go on for
también es de tiranta digo anda para
training but ugh I don't know one day I'll
entrenar pero buf no sé un día me la
wear it one day I'll see for the
pongo un día me la pongo a ver para
gym s I'm
gimnasio s me la estoy
putting it on my internet is going away I need a
poniendo se me va el internet me falta
hairdryer
secador
of course it's a set let's see Josefina a
claro es un conjunto a ver Josefina un
set it's not called it's called
conjunto no se llama se llama equipación
Josefina basketball kit not a
de baloncesto Josefina no un
set a set in what
conjunto un conjunto en lo que se pone
you wear for a wedding to match not with the
usted para una boda a juego no con la
Pamela or you know a set a sweater
Pamela o tú sabes un conjunto un polito
with jeans not that they sell but
con un vaquero no que se venden pero
of course a
claro una camiseta de tiranta de los
Laker tank top of course what do you mean by
laker claro a qué te refieres con
set
conjunto
Josefina that comes with a  carona, what
Josefina a que viene con una carona
Iñigo Rejón does, what
tela lo de iñigo rejón eh tela lo de
Iñigo
Íñigo
Rejón does, thanks, thank you to all of you who
rejón gracias gracias a todos los que os
are becoming members, eh, it's really
estáis haciendo miembro eh la verdad es
spectacular, it's really
que espectacular la verdad es que
spectacular. Let's see, let's see
espectacular A ver vamos a vamos a ver
how the members are doing because the truth
cómo van los miembros porque la verdad
is that I have the bar a little
es que la barra la tengo un poco Ahí
outdated, I don't know if there are more, if there are
desactualizada no sé si hay más si hay
fewer, there are
menos hay
fewer.
menos
We have 172 members right now, eh. There's
172 miembros tenemos ahora mismo eh Hay
a little less, not much less than what
un poco menos no mucho menos de lo que
the bar says. Javi. I don't like the
pone la barra Javi No me gusta la
tank top, always, always,
camiseta de tiranta siempre siempre
always, it really doesn't fail, you
siempre siempre de verdad no falla
always find fault with everything,
siempre le ponéis pega a todo
eh. I come and I come with a pink t-shirt,
eh vengo y vengo con una camiseta Rosa
I like it, I don't like it, I love it, I don't
me gusta no me gusta me encanta no me
love it, I shave, don't shave, yes, shave, you
encanta me afeito no te afeites sí te
're better, you're worse. Damn,
afeita estás mejor estás peor
eh, fabric, fabric, fabric, eh. Alne, fabric, eh, fabric,
eh tela tela tela eh alne tela
fabric, then remind me of it in
eh tela tela tela luego recuérdamelo en
the youth center.
la chavalería
But it's not that you're like that,
pero es que no no es que sois así le
you find fault with everything. I arrive with a
ponéis peg tod llego con un peinado
different hairstyle, I love it, I love it like this.
diferente me encanta me encanta así por
Please tell me how I do it, okay, eh. And other
favor dime cómo lo hago vale eh Y otra
people, what the [ __ ]?  quick I mean really I mean I ca
gente qué [__] ráp te o sea de verdad
n't really count the truth is that's why I
O sea no puedo echar cuenta la verdad es
'm doing my own thing eh That's why I'm doing
que por eso voy a mi bola eh Por eso voy
my own thing because it's that I can't pay attention I ca
a mi bola porque es que no puedo hacer
n't pay attention the truth Let's see
caso no puedo hacer caso la verdad A ver
[ __ ] today Lili you're here Lili Lili we
[__] hoy Lili estás por aquí Lili Lili
have to tell people what you
le tenemos que contara gente lo que me
did to me today
has hecho hoy
eh I don't know if Lili is around eh
eh No sé si está la Lili por ahí eh
but listen Lili stop stop they almost ruined me
pero escucha Lili para para casi me
eh you almost ruined me Lili
eh casi me buscas la ruina Lili
eh of course let's see no no Look it doesn't come out Look
eh claro a ver no no Mira no sale Mira
how it doesn't come out of course embarrassed you she's
comoo no sale claro vergüenza te ten
there she's there Look at her
está ahí está ahí Mírala
e It turns out that the girl is talking to me
e Resulta ser que me habla la muchacha
at noon But on top of that with emojis of with
al mediodía Pero encima con emojis de
alert emojis you know like like I
con emojis de alerta sabes como en plan
know you don't pay attention to anyone but
sé que no le haces caso a nadie pero
pay attention to me
hazme
okay with the mojis of of the alarm
caso vale con el mojis de de la alarma
that one no the little red light not urgent urgent urgent urgent
esa no el pilotito rojo no urgente
and it says
urgente urgente urgente y me
Ortega Cano died I
pone ha muerto Ortega Cano
say [ __ ] what a pain I say [ __ ] the
digo [__] qué palo digo [__] la
truth is what a pain because it was you no no it's
verdad que qué palo porque era tú no no
bad you don't know and and I run away I
está malo no sabes y y cojo corriendo yo
say Well it
digo Bueno me
caught me it's it caught me around here
cogió es que me cogió por aquí
turning on  the computer And I don't know the
encendiendo el ordenador Y eso no sé la
truth But it caught me here to
verdad Pero me cogió por aquí para
start working let's say to start
ponerme a trabajar vamos para ponerme a
recording newscasts and so on I go
grabar noticieros y y
into Google
demás me meto en Google
you I put Ortega Cano first news item he has
ti t pongo Ortega Cano primera noticia
died Ortega
ha muerto ha muerto Ortega
Cano has died and I say
Cano y digo
damn it also said this they have edited it
[__] además ponía esto lo han editado
right
verdad
Lili now it says El Torero José
Lili ahora pone muere El Torero José
Ortega dies at 75 this they have edited it
Ortega a los 75 esto lo han editado
right Let's see wait I'm going to check it
verdad A ver espérate lo voy a comprobar
José Ortega doesn't die it's that eh No no well it said
no muere José Ortega es que eh No no
José Ortega Eh well it said
pues ponía José Ortega Eh pues ponía
this morning it said José Ortega Lili or it
esta mañana ponía José Ortega Lili o
said Ortega Cano because I know that I
ponía Ortega Cano porque yo sé que lo
put it into Google and the first news item was
metí en Google y la primera noticia era
El Torero José Ortega
muere El Torero José Ortega
Cano dies I could have sworn it said Ortega Cano eh of
Cano yo juraría que ponía Ortega Cano eh
course let's see it's José Ortega and they made a
claro a ver es José Ortega y se han
mistake and they put Ortega
equivocado y han puesto Ortega
Cano then you go into the news item and it comes
Cano luego te metes en la noticia y
out Look if it says it here look at the
sale Mira si lo pone aquí mira el
matador of everything what the [ __ ] [ __ ] a
matador de todo es que [__] [__] un
José Ortega Cano also who is also
José Ortega Cano también que que también
dedicated to bullfighting and also more or  less than
se dedica al toreo y además más o menos
the same age you say [ __ ] me [ __ ]
de la misma edad dices tú [__] me cago
one day of course it said Ortega Cano yes
un dí claro ponía Ortega Cano que sí
Lili it said Ortega Cano and it's José Ortega
Lili ponía Ortega Cano y es José Ortega
Ríos they've edited it eh they've edited it
Ríos la han editado eh la han editado
[ __ ] now I can't know eh
[__] ahora no lo puedo saber eh No
We haven't taken a screenshot or anything eh but
hemos sacado captura ni nada eh pero
anyway I
total Yo
start I think I opened live eh I got
empiezo creo que abrí directo eh llegué
to open live because I was going I say why am
a abrir directo porque iba digo para qué
I going to record a video or whatever I
voy a grabar un vídeo o lo que sea me
go live in a moment we read the
pongo en directo en un momento leemos la
news we react no because of course
noticia reaccionamos no porque claro
this is Ortega Cano I [ __ ] in 10
esto es que es Ortega Cano me cago en 10
you know and recording the video no No
sabes y y grabando el vídeo no No
lie I was going to go live and I think I
mentira me iba a poner en directo y creo
even programmed it I started it or something
que incluso lo program lo inicié o algo
and and and I say I'm going to record it from my
y y y digo lo voy a grabar desde el
phone and recording the video I say family
móvil y grabando el vídeo digo familia
What sad news how strong Because
Qué triste noticia qué fuerte Porque
also a while ago like half an
además hacía un rato hacía como media
hour ago another news story came out in La
hora había salido otra noticia en la
Reason and in all the media that José
razón y en todos los medios de que José
Ortega Cano this morning was in the
orte canano esta mañana estado en el
hospital to get checked out for the
hospital para revisarse el tema de la
fall from the other time and so on no eh And
caída de la otra vez y demás no eh Y
I say [ __ ] look  you who has gone to the
digo [__] fíjate tú que ha ido al
hospital and will know that whatever it is is complicated
hospital y sabrá complicado lo que sea
there that the man has died okay I'll
allí que se ha muerto el hombre vale me
go first Javi next time
meto en lo primero Javi para la próxima
Turn on the TV no no he didn't do it Lorena I say
Enciende la tele no no lo hizo Lorena
Lorena has died stingy
digo Lorena se ha muerto tacano madre
my goodness he says I'm going to turn on the TV what will they
mía dice voy a encender la tele que
be Talking about them and he says How
estarán Hablando de ellos y dice Qué
strange nobody talks about this I start
raro nadie habla de esto me pongo a
recording a video with my cell phone of these
grabar vídeo con el móvil de estos
videos with my cell phone No here the cell phone
vídeos con el móvil No aquí el móvil
here below on the desk and I say look
aquí abajo en el escritorio y digo mira
family Well look at the news in the
familia Pues mira la noticia en el
hospital I don't know what I don't know how much and when I
hospital no sé qué no sé cuánto y cuando
say to myself I'm going to read you the news I
me digo os voy a leer la noticia
open it and when I start to read I
abro y cuando empiezo a leer me doy
realize that it wasn't and I say to her Lili Lili it's that we
cuenta que no era y le digo Lili Lili es
would have made a Lidia loano we would have
que hubiéramos liado una Lidia loano nos
made a Lidia loano here
hubiéramos marcado un Lidia loano aquí
eh totally eh I
eh totalmente
mean tremendous
eh o sea tremendo
eh very tremendous and Gloria Camila also
eh tremendísimo y gloria Camila también
says of course Gloria Camila must have told her
dice claro Gloria Camila le habrá dicho
something they have changed him and she says another news
algo lo han cambiado y dice otra noticia
a bit clumsy dad is alive and
un poco trambólico papá está vivito y
kicking and may it be so for many
coleando y que así sea por muchos años
more years let's see it's normal these are things that happen he's
más a ver es normal son cosas que pasan
a rat in the end their names are almost the
es una rata al final son nombres casi
same  no and and these are things that happen but damn [ __ ]
iguales no y y son cosas que pasan pero
eh [ __ ] thank
[__] [__] eh
goodness he has a very
[__] menos mal tiene un chavalito muy
young boy, let's see Alicia Sure but it's
pequeño a ver Alicia Claro ya pero
also that she had the
también es que ha tenido el
boy when he was too old to be a
chavalito siendo demasiado mayor para
boy let's see You can do what
chavalito a ver Tú puedes hacer lo que
you want but of course these are things that more
tú quieras pero claro son cosas que más
or
o
less are things that more or less I
menos son cosas que más o menos
couldn't let's see the law of life I hope not
no podría a ver ley de vida Ojalá que no
I hope not but well it's the law of
Ojalá que no pero bueno es ley de
life Well let's talk a little about
vida Bueno vamos a comentar un poco lo
Íñigo Rejón Although this channel is not
de Íñigo rejón Aunque este canal no sea
political no but the fact is that this is
político no pero es que esto es salseo
political gossip and the truth is that this
político y es que esto la verdad es que
is very strong you're telling me that it
es muy fuerte me estáis diciendo que se
went on today it's not like we were there for an
ha alargado hoy el ni que fuéramos una
hour To talk about Rejón how strong No
hora Para hablar de rejón qué fuerte No
how strong No look first let's watch
qué fuerte No mira primero vamos a ver
the summary of illustrated news and
el resumen de noticias ilustradas y
then we'll see a little The screenshots
después vamos a ver un poco Las capturas
that have been published and what people are
que se han publicado y lo que está
commenting on and so on eh but to
comentando la peña y demás eh pero para
give you an idea Iñigo Rejón
que os hagáis una idea iñigo rejón
is a
es
politician one of the leaders of Tenos
político de de los cabecillas de tenos
at the time now he was good at adding okay it's that it does
en su momento ahora lo era de sumar vale
n't fail it's that he's a mathematician
es que no falla es que es matemático
always uncle is mathematical or rather The
siempre tío es matemático o sea Cuanto
more
más
allies and it is splashing more here in
aliades y está salpicando a más aquí en
aini the more
aini cuanto más
allies the more sexist in truth and the more
aliades más machista en verdad y más
these things everything is like a role that
estas cosas todo es como un papel que
they play to win the votes of The
hacen para para ganarse los votos de Los
idiots
idiotas
Look Okay now we are seeing it okay
Mira Bueno ahora lo vamos viendo vale
But so that you understand me it is This look there
Pero para que me entendáis es Este mira
are no false accusations there is a
no hay denuncias falsas hay una derecha
fanatical right whose job is to criminalize
fanática cuyo trabajo es criminalizar a
women Okay now it is to subtract he did not
las mujeres Vale ahora es de restar no
put the tweet also to Rosito the
le puso el tweet también a a rosito el
typical tweet of I do believe you sister
típico tweet de yo si te creo hermana
Look here I put it look Yes I do
Mira por aquí lo puse yo mira Sí yo sí
believe you Rocío Carrasco denounced
te creo Rocío Carrasco denunció ayer la
sexist violence yesterday a testimony of
violencia machista un testimonio de
abuse that many will question
maltrato que muchos pondrán en duda
just as they did with Nana Orantes
igual que lo hicieron con Nana Orantes
just as they have done with so
igual que lo han hecho con tantas y
many women that is why feminism is so necessary
tantas mujeres por eso es tan necesario
while I was
el feminismo mientras que estaba
doing this in 2021 I had already
haciendo esto en el 2021 ya lo había
done eh my thing eh the close date was there
hecho eh lo suyo eh estaba ahí la fecha
Look here we are going to see it in
cercana Mira por aquí lo vamos a ver en
the summary but it is like that they are it is a
el resumen pero es que es así son es
lie The more they want to give it to them
mentira Cuanto más se la quieran dar
but whether they are politicians or youtuber eh or or
pero ya sean políticos o youtuber eh o o
whoever it is eh but The more allies
quien sea eh pero Cuanto más de aliades
want to give it to him The more
se la quieran dar Cuanto más aliades
feminist allies I don't know what I don't know how much they
feministes no sé qué no sé cuánto se la
want to give it to him there there you have it there
quieran dar ahí ahí lo tienes tú ahí lo
you have it eh There are times when it's to
tienes tú eh Hay veces que es para para
dip the churro and there are other times when it's to
mojar el churro y hay otras veces que es
win votes from the
pues para para ganar votos de Los
idiots and simply line their pockets
idiotas y llenarse los bolsillos
ex of podemos and current
simplemente ex de podemos y actual
spokesperson for suar in congress resigns
portavoz de suar en el congreso dimite
Why I summarize it all for you it starts
Por qué te lo resumo todo comienza hace
a year ago in June 2023 on Twitter an
un año en junio de 2023 en Twitter una
anonymous account tells of an event that had
cuenta anónima cuenta un suceso que
occurred with rejón this tweet
había ocurrido con el rejón este tweet
was deleted Shortly after but several
es eliminado Al poco tiempo pero varios
media outlets kept copies
medios de comunicación guardaron copias
in it the following was said on
en él se decía lo siguiente el pasado 17
June 17 I had an uncomfortable experience
de junio tuve una experiencia incómoda
with r rejon that could be considered
con r rejon que se podría considerar
sexist aggression the chick This one seems to have
agresión sexista la pava Esta se ve que
been with some friends of hers at a
estaba con unas amigas suyas en un
feminist event when suddenly he
evento feminista cuando de repente
starts groping one of her colleagues
comienza a sobar a una de sus colegas
but the girl slaps him and
pero la chica le pega un manotazo y
errejón what happens is that after a while
errejón para lo que pasa que al rato
errejón stands next to the one
errejón se pone al lado de la que
writing the tweet and begins to notice how
escribe el tweet y comienza a notar como
the politician  he's touching her uncut ass
el político le está tocando el culo sin
she is paralyzed why ca
corte ella se queda paralizada por qué
n't she understand that
no puede entender que esté sucediendo
this is happening from someone who
eso por parte de alguien que se
considers himself left-wing and feminist her
considera de izquierdas y feminista sus
friends seeing the face of the protagonist
amigas al ver la cara de la protagonista
go to her and ask if she is
van donde ella y le preguntan si está
okay but nothing is in shock Yes,
bien pero nada está en shock Eso sí
after a few minutes with a clearer mind
pasados unos minutos ya con la mente más
she goes to talk to
clara ella se va a hablar con el entorno
Rejón's environment to comment on what
de rejón para comentar lo que ha
happened And soon the politician and his
sucedido Y al poco el político y sus
friends leave the event Okay, what I just
amigos abandonan el acto Okay esto que
told you It was only at the
te acabo de contar Solamente era al
beginning because the straw that broke the camel's back
principio porque la gota que ha colmado
were some screenshots taken by
el vaso son unas capturas que ha sacado
the journalist Cristina fallarás where you can
la periodista Cristina fallarás en donde
see an Instagram conversation
se ve una conversación de Instagram
where an anonymous woman comments the
donde una mujer anónima Comenta lo
following a well-known politician from
siguiente un político muy conocido de
Madrid here he doesn't say his name who I had already been
Madrid aquí no dice el nombre al que ya
warned about the peculiar treatment he
me habían avisado del trato peculiar que
gave to women buah he's a
daba a las mujeres buah es un
psychological abuser he has to be nice
maltratador psicológico ha de simpático
to hook you but then when he
para engancharte pero luego cuando te
has you he starts blaming you for
tiene comienza a echarte la culpa de
everything in a moment he's eating your
todo en un momentico te está comiendo la
ear and in two hours he kicks you out of the house and
oreja y a las do horas te echa de casa y
if you do something he doesn't like he ignores you  that
si haces algo que no le Mola te hace el
you learn that
vacío para que vayas aprendiendo que
you have to respect him like a God which
tienes que respetarle como un Dios que
is what he thinks he is also his
es lo que él se cree que es además su
way of having sex is more like he
forma de tener sexo es más como si él
's masturbating with your body he
estuviese masturbándose con tu cuerpo te
asks you to do humiliating things and if you don't
pide hacer cosas humillantes y si no las
do them he'll give you a hard time and there's more
haces te monta un pollo y hay más cosas
But I prefer not to tell them I'm sure
Pero prefiero no contarlas seguro que
other women can corroborate that he is
otras mujeres pueden corroborar que es
a true psychopath and a monster
un verdadero psicópata y un monstruo
all these captures when they relate
todas estas capturas al se relacionan
to the figure they always cancel the
con la figura siempre cancelan a los
allies eh yesterday we were precisely
aliades eh ayer precisamente estábamos
talking about hapl shaffer about
hablando lo de hapl shaffer lo de
roldier I mean we're talking about all
roldier o sea estamos hablando de todos
these that go from no no I'm the most
estos que van de no no yo soy el más de
built I point out the others I do this I do it It doesn't
construido yo señalo a los demás yo esto
fail dude it doesn't [ __ ] fail dude It doesn't
yo lo No falla tío no [__] falla tío No
fail It doesn't
falla No
fail from rejón and things are getting
falla de rejón y la cosa se pone
heated up to the fact that his own
caliente hasta el hecho de que su propio
party adds He opens an investigation
partido sumar Abre una investigación la
which hasn't given much time to
cual no ha dado mucho tiempo a que
advance because this morning the rejón
avance porque esta mañana el rejón les
sent them a letter to announce his
ha mandado una carta para anunciar su
resignation the party has listened to the
dimisión el partido ha escuchado las
reasons why he resigned and has
razones por las que se pinaba y ha
accepted his departure saying that
aceptado su marcha diciendo que hay que
a feminist society and politics must be built
construir una sociedad y política
and for that they  It requires
feminista y Para ello se requiere el
commitment from all areas. This
compromiso de todos los ámbitos esta
letter was later published and
carta de rejón luego ha sido publicada y
in it the politician says the following: the
en ella el político dice lo siguiente el
pace and way of life on the front line of
ritmo y modo de vida en primera línea de
politics has worn down my
la política ha desgastado mi salud
physical, mental health, affective and
física mental y estructura afectiva y
emotional structure. In other words, he wanted to leave
emocional O sea que se ha querido ir
as someone he wasn't, that's why no. In other words, he did
como el que no era por eso
n't leave because he said, Hey, I have to
no O sea no se ha ido por decir Oye
resign because look, I've done
tengo que dimitir porque mira he hecho
something that doesn't correspond with what
una cosa que no corresponde con lo que
I'm preaching, no, eh? No,
estoy predicando no
no, he tried to pass it off as if he
eh No no lo ha intentado colar como que
left because he suddenly wore himself out
se ha ido porque se ha desgastado de
and this has generated a
repente y esto ha generado una
toxic subjectivity that, in the case of
subjetividad tóxica que en el caso de
men, the patriarchy multiplies
los hombres el patriarcado multiplica
with his male and female colleagues. He
con los compañeros y compañeras del
also acknowledges that he has been
trabajo además reconoce que lleva tiempo
in psychological support for some time and that he
en acompañamiento psicológico y que
needs to leave politics to
necesita abandonar la política para
take care of himself. He also comments that you can't
cuidarse además comenta no se le puede
ask people to vote differently than
pedir a la gente que vote distinto de
how they behave in their daily lives. And
cómo se comporta en su vida cotidiana y
for now, That's all you know,
de momento Eso es todo lo que sabe tú
what do you think? Come on, I'll
qué piensas venga que te
read you, but I don't have to kiss you,
leo pero no a m a d tienen que beso
bichi. Jai, for God's sake, how handsome, beautiful, you, beautiful, you, I mean, I
bichi Jai por Dios qu guapo guapa tú
mean, Marina Lobo knew it, no,
o sea o sea Marina Lobo lo sabía no
aini, Marina Lobo, for example,  I knew
aini Marina Lobo por ejemplo lo sabía
why she posted a tweet saying, well, it
porque ha puesto un tweet diciendo pues
was about time, half of Spain knew,
Ya era hora la mitad de España lo sabía
and the other half was covering it up, and she, she
Y la otra mitad lo encubría y ella ella
hadn't said
no había dicho
anything.
nada
No, man, these are moments when I
no tío esto Estos son unos momentos que
really have a good time, eh. These
la verdad me lo paso muy bien eh Estos
are moments when I laugh a lot,
son unos momentos que que me río mucho
eh. These are moments when I laugh a
eh Estos son unos momentos que me río
lot. Look, I do believe you, Roso
mucho Mira yo sí te creo roso
Carrasco, but on top of that, the
Carrasco pero es que encima El
scoundrel of the time wanted to leave
sinvergüenza de la época ha querido irse
like the one who wasn't,
como el que como el que no era por esto
like the one who was
como el que se
leaving. Oh, really, they are the best.
iba Ay de verdad es que son la [__]
Look, look, look, the little
Mira mira mira mira el
character. This is not the same one who
personajillo Este no es el mismo que le
kicked an old man. I'm just saying that
pegó una patada a un viejo Yo es que la
political issues,
la los temas políticos los salseos
political gossip and so on, an older man, an
políticos y demás a un hombre mayor a un
older man, eh, old people are the
hombre mayor eh viejos son los son los
furniture and the rags, people are
muebles y los trapos las personas somos
older, but he kicked him, he kicked him,
mayores pero le pegó una le pegó un
not an older man, he didn't start
patón no a un hombre mayor no se puso a
kicking grandparents, it
patear abuelos no
wasn't this same one. No, I saw it in,
era este mismo No yo vi en
eh. Well, look, I was just
eh Pues mira ahora os estaba
mentioning you, the Indian was acquitted of that.
mencionando salió absuelto de eso el
But why was he acquitted, what
indio Pero por qué salió absuelto qué
reason did he not kick him?  or
motivo porque no le pego la patada o
because it was a fight blah blah blah I
porque era una bronca patatín patatán o
mean I saw monedero a monedero I saw him
sea yo vi a monedero a monedero lo vi yo
the other day in in the the other day it was
el otro día en en la en el otro día era
a month month and a half or two I don't know one of the
un mes mes y pico o dos no sé una de las
last times I went to Madrid I don't know
últimas veces que fui Madrid no sé que
what I was there for and I was in El
para qué estaba yo allí y estaba en el
Retiro I took a walk through El Retiro
retiro me pegué un paseo por el retiro
with the kids and that and and and I saw him in
con los niños y eso y y y lo vi en el
Javi you reacted to an incident Ofelia
Javi reaccionaste a un incidente Ofelia
a kiss beautiful sweetheart I love you the
un beso guapa corazón Te quiero el
whole neighborhood for you my weapon Oh there's
barrio entero para ti mi arma Ah que que
no proof there's no proof that she
no hay prueba que no hay prueba de que
kicked the man okay okay okay okay And
pateó al hombre vale vale vale vale Y
what's wrong with her here it worries me
aquí qué es lo que le pasa me preocupa
that in our country since 2003
que en nuestro país que desde 2003 han
thousands of women have died in our country have been
muerto miles de mujeres en nuestro país
murdered eidas raped let's not
han asesinadas a edidas violadas no nos
take ourselves seriously we have a scourge
tomemos En serio que tenemos una lacra
called sexist violence
que se llama violencia machista
violence is that they are like that man let's see
violencia es que son así tío a ver
obviously We should
evidentemente Nosotros sí tendríamos que
respect the presumption of innocence no
respetar la presunción de inocencia no
because What evidence is there so far
porque Qué pruebas hay hasta el momento
a few testimonies Of course What
unos cuantos testimonios Claro Lo que
happens is that according to what they preach we
pasa que según lo que ellos predican
would have to go to the
tendríamos que tendríamos que ir a
death for  for the testimony of the
muerte a por a por el testimonio de la
alleged victim and to the sack and treat him
presunta víctima y a saco y tratarlo ya
as an abuser according to what he
como un maltratador según lo que él
preaches, it worries me that in our country, where
predica me preocupa que en nuestro país
thousands of women have died since 2003
que desde 2003 han muerto miles de
in our country, murdered,
mujeres en nuestro país asesinadas
attacked, raped, we do not take ourselves
agredidas violadas no nos tomemos En
seriously, that we have a scourge called
serio que tenemos una lacra que se llama
sexist violence, violence against
violencia machista violencia contra las
women, it worries me that in our country,
mujeres me preocupa que en nuestro país
how heavy,
qué heavy
eh, this is a video from 2017, if it
Eh Esto que es un vídeo del 2017 si no
weren't for how serious the subject is, you could
fuera por lo serio del tema se podría
say that Iñigo Rejón's Twitter profile
decir que el perfil en Twitter de iñigo
has become a
rejón se ha convertido en una cuenta
parody account, of course, of course, it's not
parodia Claro claro claro es que no es
a clip, it's that this is all the time,
un cli Es que esto es todo el tiempo
of course, it's not to say that you
claro no es decir que de este hombre te
can find a clip from this man in which he
puedas encontrar un cli en el que hace
alludes to what is happening to
alusión a lo que ahora le está pasando a
him now, no, it's not that it's all, of course, it's what he is, it's what
él no no es que es todo claro es lo que
his
é es lo que es su
thing is, look at how women continue to
movida mira que las mujeres sigan
endure stereotypes,
soportando cada día estereotipos
prejudices, and inequality every day, I mean,
perjuicios y desigualdad o sea es que
this is so you can see that it
esto es para que ustedes veáis que
's always a lie, it's a [ __ ] role that
siempre es mentira es un [__] papel que
they play to win votes from people who are
hacen para ganar votos de gente que es
stupid and believe that  These people are
tonta y se cree que esta gente son así
really like allies for women I don't know
de verdad aliades por las mujeres no sé
what I don't know
qué no sé
how much I mean literally it's that
cuánto o sea literalmente es eso
eh literally it's that eh I mean look
eh literalmente es eso eh o sea fíjate
No, the truth is that while
No que la verdad es que mientras que
while he was preaching this he was
mientras que iba predicando esto iba
doing the other supposedly behind people's
haciendo lo otro supuestamente por las
backs it's not like it's not like a child
espaldas no es como no es como un niño
mixed with an
mezclado con un
old man Of course, of course he said that
viejito Claro claro él decía que Las
False accusations don't exist So
denuncias falsas no existen Entonces
this I
esto
understand no Loreto Arenillas, deputy of
entiendo no Loreto arenillas diputada de
Madrid and former chief of staff of Íñigo
m Madrid y exjefa de gabinete de Íñigo
Rejón pressured at least one woman so
rejón presionó al menos a una mujer para
that you don't denounce Íñigo so as not to
que no denuncias a Íñigo para no
subject him to public ridicule
someterle a escarnio público lo sabía
the whole party knew about it including Mónica García
todo el partido incluida Mónica García
who supported them both my goodness of course they
que les mantuvo los dos madre mía claro
are like that man they are like that they are this is
es que son así tío es que son así
a business I mean they are a
son esto es un negocio o sea son un
role each one takes a role Hey, well
papel cada uno pilla un papel Oye pues
I take the role of ally and another
yo Pillo el papel de aliade y otro
party Well I ask for the role of
partido Pues yo pido el papel de
socialist you understand me I mean look at you
socialista me entiendes o sea fíjate tú
today in the kids Precisely in the
hoy en la chavalería Precisamente en el
news I'm going to publish a story about the
noticiero voy a publicar una noticia del
PSOE playing  cont de gref or rather
psoe jugando cont de gref o sea
trying to arm wrestle de gref
intentando hacerle un pulso a de gref
over the taxes thing Uy uy
por el tema de los es los impuestos Uy
uy uy uy uy this is a business this
uy uy uy uy uy esto es un negocio esto
is a
es un
joke look today Uy Today there's a lot of
cachondeo mira hoy Uy Hoy hay mucho tema
political talk Today there's a lot of political gossip
político Hoy hay mucho salseo político
because the streamers are on
porque están los streamers
The streamers are on fire let's
Ardiendo están los streamers
see
a ver
Wal
Wal
St [ __ ] How do you spell Wall Street
St [__] Cómo se escribe Wall Street
wolbring let's
wolbring a
see now
ver ahora
[ __ ] look wait wait wait wait wait
[__] mira
this
espera esto
man wait wait I'm going to put the list
tío espera Espera voy a poner la lista
better this man are the
mejor esto tío son las cuotas de
self-employed fees next year it's worth whoever
autónomo el año que viene vale el que
earns less than
gane menos de
700 whoever earns less than
700 el que gane menos de
700 monthly fee of 200 30
700 cuota mensual de 200 30
bucks how are you going to charge a person
pavos cómo le vas a cobrar a una persona
who earns
que cobre
670 500
670 500
600 400 how are you going to charge a fee
600 400 cómo le vas a cobrar una cuota
of
de
230 plus taxes of course
230 más los impuestos claro
obviously this is the self-employed fee
evidentemente esto es la cuota autónomo
eh or rather plus taxes
eh o sea más los impuestos
plus taxes plus 20% blah
más los impuestos más el 20% el patatín
blah blah it's worth or rather between 670 and 900 250
patatán vale o sea entre 670 y 900 250
of
de
quota That is to say
cuota O sea a
250 to people who generate less than 1000 euros as self-employed,
250 a gente que que genere de autónomo
let's
vamos te
tell you. I consider that from
digo yo Considero que a partir
this section more or less from this, that is to
de este tramo más o menos desde este o
say, there should be no
sea no debería haber
quota. How are you going to charge a quota to people
cuota cómo le vas a cobrar cuota a gente
who generate 100,
que genere 100
1600, 300 euros of
1600 300 pavos de
quota, that is to say at least from yes,
cuota o sea como mínimo a partir de sí
people who earn 2000 who generate 2000,
gente que gane 2000 que genere 2000
1700, well,
1700 bueno
but from there down, how are you going to
pero de ahí para abajo cómo le vas a
charge self-employed quotas? No, no, no, well, they
cobrar cuotas de autónomo no no no pues
charge and it is a third, okay. Well, a
se cobra y es un tercio vale Bueno un
third in the case of these people is almost
tercio en el caso de esta gente es casi
half because here we are not counting
la mitad porque aquí no estamos contando
taxes, eh, the personal income tax and what they
de los impuestos eh el irpf y lo que te
take from you, eh, it is legal theft, eh, I mean, the issue of the
quitan eh es un robo legal eh o sea el
self-employed, the issue of
tema de los autónomos el tema de los
taxes in Spain, eh, we are
impuestos en España eh lo estamos
assuming it. We are not protesting or
asumiendo No estamos protestando ni
doing anything, okay, look, it is that
estamos haciendo nada vale mira es que
in itself you say, well, the one who earns
ya de por sí dices tú bueno el que gana
money, it seems to me that from a
dinero es que me parece que de una
person who generates
persona que genere
6000, the self-employed quota would be
6000 que la cuota de autónomos fueran
600  let's say it is from 2025, that
600 vamos que lo es a partir del 2025 o
is, in 3 months it is
sea dentro de 3 meses es un
10%, it is 10%,
10% es un 10%
man, it is a legal robbery, it is a robbery that has been
tío es un robo legal es un robo que se
legalized
ha ido legalizando
and we assume it. And we do not protest and we
y lo asumimos Y no protestamos y nos
get used to, well, we have the rest
acostumbramos a bueno tenemos el resto
of what we have left or well, let's
de lo que nos queda o bueno vamos a
do it illegally, let them pay me
vamos a hacerlo en negro que me paguen
illegally in the business, let them pay me because I do
en negro en el negocio que me paguen que
not have a dataphone, we have not gotten used
no tengo datáfono no nos hemos habituado
to that, man, and what we have to do is
a eso tío y lo que hay que hacer es
go out on the
salir a la
streets, not vote for anyone who is not going to
calle no votar a nadie que no vaya a
change this, I mean, whoever earns
cambiar esto o sea es que el que gane
6,000, whoever earns 6,000, 10% you have to
6000 el que gane 6000 un 10%
give it to these pieces of
se lo tienes que dar a estos pedazos de
[ __ ] and then out of what you have left, of
cabrones y luego de lo que te queda de
the 5,400 that you have left, they are going to take
los 5400 que te quedan de ahí te van a
away from you, we are talking
quitar estamos hablando
about 50, 600,000 a year, out of 60,000 a
que serían 50 600000 al año de 60.000 al
year they take away approximately 30 and a
año te quitan aproximadamente un 30 y
bit, yes,
pico por c Sí o
in the end you are going to be left, out of every
sea al final te vas a quedar de de cada
6,000 you are going to  stay with 4000
6000 te vas a quedar con 4000
But Javi there are people who justify
Pero Javi que hay gente que justifica
this even today because I've seen
esto hoy todavía porque yo he visto
people on the left Even today clutching their
gente de izquierda Incluso hoy echándose
heads with this
la mano a la cabeza con esta
table you know what happens normally the
tabla sabéis Qué pasa que normalmente la
people who
gente que
vote of course make up the majority and they vote for
vota claro hacen mayoría y votan
parties that give little aid and that give a
partidos que dan ayuditas y que dan un
lot of little things no but in reality they
montón de cositas no pero en realidad te
put it here to the people who
la meten por aquí a la gente que que
generate the money of
genera el dinero
course This is to go out on the streets eh
claro Esto es para salir a la calle eh
family and say that nothing is paid This
familia y decir que no se paga nada Esto
is to go out on the streets and say everything
es para salir a la calle y decir todo
all the self-employed everyone
todos los autónomos todos todos
absolutely all the self-employed in the
absolutamente todos los autónomos del
country say we don't pay a [ __ ] fee
país decir no pagamos ni una [__] cuota
until this becomes logical and
hasta que esto se se haga lógico y
normal taxes Yes but well but
normal impuestos Sí pero bueno pero
logical it's not that you know Who creates
lógicos no es que sabéis Quiénes crean
these tables these tables are decided by
estas tablas estas tablas las deciden
people who set their salary
gente que se pone el sueldo que le da la
however they want well this year I'm going to raise it
gana pues este año me lo voy a subir
well this year Well I'm going to raise it and I'm
pues este año Bueno me lo voy a subir y
going to take the credit card and I'm going to
voy a [__] la tarjeta y me me lo voy a
spend it on cocaine and [ __ ] you
gastar en cocaína y en [__] me
understand I mean we've normalized that they
entendéis o sea hemos normalizado que
steal from us and turn the other cheek dude it doesn't make
nos roben y poner la otra mejilla tío no
any [ __ ] sense  But yes there is a lot of
tiene putísimo sentido Pero sí hay mucho
political gossip eh today eh you loaded
salseo político eh hoy eh has cargado a
isco [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] Miserable scum I
isco zorra [__] zorra Escoria miserable
wish you everything that can happen to you in
te deseo todo lo que te pueda pasar en
life bad They told Sara
la vida malo Esto se lo dijeron a Sara
Salamo I would give anything to see your
sálamo darí lo que fuera por verte las
tits Sara Salamo is the actress no Sara
tetas Sara salamo es la actri no Sara
Salam is not the actress this one who is very
salam no es la la actriz esta que es muy
pretty she is a woman if I'm not mistaken
guapa que es mujer si no me equivoco de
a soccer player it's that girl who
un futbolista es que esa chica me me
wrote to me once yes she is the one I think she
escribió una vez si es la que yo pienso
wrote to me but I don't remember
me escribió pero no me acuerdo el Por
why it was I mean she wrote to me because she posted
qué fue o sea me escribió porque puso
some nonsense supporting these parties
una tontería apoyando a estos partidos
but I don't remember what it was I mean I don't think I was
pero no me acuerdo que era O sea no creo
disrespectful to her In any case maybe
que le faltase el respeto En todo caso a
some mockery some joke but you
lo mejor alguna burla alguna broma pero
know he
sabes me me
wrote to me and said something like
escribió y me dijo algo así como
Oh I saw you on la sexto and it seemed very
Ay te vi en la sexta y me pareció muy
strong what they did to you Do not participate
fuerte Lo que te hicieron No participes
in what they do to me and I almost tell you
en lo que me hacen a mí y me cas digo
that you have already gone a little crazy no
que ya se te ha ido un poco la olla no
guilla I mean a note
guilla O sea me está comparando un nota
that I have here is comparing me that leaks my address that
que tengo aquí que filtra mi dirección
makes child pornography with
que que me hace pornografía infantil con
my children and that threatens me to kill you that
mis hijos y que me amenaza de muerte que
I do you  a mockery of a political issue, the thing
yo te haga una burla de tema
about free highways,
rosón lo de autopista gratis colegio
free school and all that stuff doesn't fly anymore, it's not a joke
gratis y esas cosas ya no cuela roscón
when you're seeing them with
cuando te los estás viendo con
companions, with 25 advisors, with a
acompañantes con 25 asesores con un
Falcon, with prostitutes who catch three
Falcón con prostitutas que pillan a tres
or four members of the party taking cocaine in
o cuatro del partido tomando cocaína en
a hotel, I don't know what, I don't know how much, and
un hotel que no sé qué no sé cuánto y y
in the end everyone leaves Rosita's house. I
se van al final todo el mundo de Rosita
mean, the highways and all that stuff doesn't fly anymore,
O sea ya no cuela lo de las autopistas y
I think that the highways
lo de eso ya yo creo que las autopistas
and the healthcare and everything without corruption
y la sanidad y todo sin corrupción se
could be paid for with what we
podría pagar con que los que
self-employed generate worth 25%, wouldn't that
generamos los autónomos vale un 25% no
be right of what we earn 25%
estaría bien de lo que ganamos un
25% wouldn't be
25 20 25% no sería
enough 50% is a lot of cloth. No, the
suficiente un 50 es mucha tela No ya la
excuse
excusa
of while you're idiots, that's how it is, no, no,
de mientras que tontos así está no no
the highways and the hospitals and the
las autopistas y los hospitales y los
schools, the highways and the hospitals, there
colegios las autopistas y los hospitales
's Pedro
está Pedro
Sánchez. Give me another one. Give me another bottle of
Sánchez Ponme otro Ponme Otra botella de
champagne, Javi, those of us who are not
champán Javi que los que no somos
self-employed pay more than you, it
autónomos pagamos más que vosotros me
seems outrageous to me, I know, I know, I know, you know
parece una barbaridad ya lo sé ya lo sé
what happens, that those who
ya lo sé sabes qué pasa que que los que
work for someone else, like, no, like  They do
trabajan por cuenta ajena como que no
n't notice it so directly because you
como que no lo notan tan directo porque
already collect, not with everything taken away,
ya cobras no con todo lo quitado
the self-employed you collect it and then they take it from you.
los autónomos lo cobras y luego te lo
Oh really, I mean, it's brutal, eh, it
quitan Ay de verdad o sea es brutal eh
's brutal, like on top of that, we still
es brutal como como encima todavía
justify being robbed, eh, that's
justificamos que nos roben eh eso se
called in my town on top of being a [ __ ] and
llama en mi pueblo encima de [__] y
forgive me for the expression, eh. But in
perdonadme la expresión eh Pero eso en
my town, that's called on top of being a [ __ ],
mi pueblo se llama encima de [__]
beaten up, and then we have Sol Aire who
apaleado y luego tenemos a sol aire que
says first world problems, man,
dice problemas del primer mundo hombre
if it seems like the first world to you, that we
si te parece primer mundo que que
just saw a table that people who
acabamos de ver una tabla que gente que
earn 800 or 300 have 300 taken from them, plus
genere 800 o 300 le quiten 300 má más
then the declaration, well, you tell me
luego la declaración pues ya tú me dirás
if that's the first world, the third. So
si eso es el primer mundo el tercero
what are you, a selfish hick that you've
qué eres una cateta egoísta que te has
screwed up your life at 23 years old, Laura
[__] la vida con 23 años a Laura
Escanes, you're uglier than hitting a
escanes eres más fea que pegar a un
father with an Ah, that's that, Ah, okay,
padre con un Ah que está que que Ah vale
okay, that's that, she's collected, no, she's
vale que está que ha recopilado no que
collected insults to famous people,
ha recopilado insultos a famosas
sweaty, cin, imbecile, [ __ ] to Cristina,
cín sudado Cerda imbécil [__] a Cristina
Pedroche, I hope they rape you and all
pedroche ojalá te violen a ti y a todos
your children, [ __ ] to  Lidia betman [ __ ] you
tus hijos [__] a Lidia betman [__]
are a bitter woman crazy and a
eres una mujer amargada una loca y una
scoundrel to Monica Garcia what a push
Sinvergüenza a Mónica García qué empujón
you have you daughter of a [ __ ] to Mrs. Ayuso you
tienes hija de [__] a la señora Ayuso tú
are stupid illiterate you are in need of
eres tonta analfabeta estás para
medication [ __ ] This was told
medicarte [__] Esto me lo dijeron
to me And this your lordships is
a mí Y esto señorías es violencia
digital violence and it happens to all of us women,
digital y nos pasa a todas las mujeres
known, unknown, left-wing or
conocidas desconocidas de izquierdas o
right-wing and you know, you know what also
de derechas y saben saben también nos
happens to us is that when we
pasa lo que nos pasa es que cuando
open social networks many times
abrimos las redes sociales muchas veces
we find this
nos encontramos con esto lo
V This girl is stupid or what's wrong with her
V Esta tía es tonta o qué le pasa
Indo
Indo
bastard
cabrón
doesn't want the socialist state to
no el quiera estado socialista se
go away exo
vaya exo
very stupid or what's wrong with her also putting
muy tonta o qué le pasa también poniendo
that there she warned ini but she
eso ahí te lo avisó a ini pero me lo
warned me already [ __ ] when when I had it on
avisó ya [__] cuando cuando lo tenía
top of her she thinks that they can't ban you from
encima piensa que no te pueden banear de
Twitch to watch on YouTube on YouTube it
Twitch a ver en YouTube en YouTube se
cuts out and that's it it cuts out Oh my mother
corta y y ya está se corta Ay la madre
who gave birth to me I'm going to remove it so that it can't
que me parió voy a quitar para que no se
be rewound so that you can't see it I'm going
pueda rebobinar para que no lo veáis voy
to remove the ability to rewind and
a quitar que se pueda rebobinar y en
as soon as we finish the live we'll
cuanto terminemos el directo lo lo
cut it but this chick is stupid or what  what's
cortamos pero esta pava es tonta o qué
wrong with him I mean what the [ __ ] is he doing that for I had to
le pasa o sea para qué [__] hace eso
pixelate it because it's an
he tenido que pixelar lo porque es una
unwanted photo from a stranger Oh it
foto no deseada de un desconocido Ah que
's
está
pixelated it's
pixelada que está
pixelated it's bald you know how
pixelada que está pelada saben lo
violent it is to receive a photo
violento que es recibir una foto de
like this this man in
estas características a este hombre a
10 minutes he's going to be forgotten
los 10 minutos se le va a ver olvidado
but we dislike it it generates
pero a nosotras nos desagrada nos genera
a tremendous discomfort an
un un malestar tremendo una violencia
inexplicable violence it's as if it's normal for us
inexplicable es como si tuviera normal
to remain silent after having
quedarnos calladas después de haber
received a penis as if it were a toll
recibido un pene como si fuera un peaje
we have to pay for being women
que tenemos que pagar por ser mujeres
gentlemen of this chamber you are
señores de esta cámara son ustedes unos
privileged to have
privilegiados por no haber recibido
never received a photo like that ladies of this
nunca una foto así señoras de esta
chamber let's say enough we can't take it anymore we have to
cámara digamos basta no podemos más hay
stop being silent and use
que dejar de estar calladas y poner
all the tools at our
todas las herramientas que hay a nuestro
disposal to put an end to digital violence
alcance para acabar con la violencia
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
and These are the publications that he has I
y Estas son las publicaciones que ha o
mean The screenshots that he has published you
sea Las capturas que ha publicado
will fail that well if you want to stop him
fallarás que bueno si queréis pararlo
stop him okay But we have already seen it in
pararlo vale Pero ya lo hemos visto en
the
el
video I'm going to do the same Okay and here is the
vídeo voy a hacer lo mismo Vale y est la
letter that we have also summarized I
carta de que también la hemos resumido O
mean we have heard it summarized in the
sea la hemos escuchado resumida en el
video What  scoundrel
vídeo Qué sinvergüenza
eh a classic of
eh un clásico de los psicópatas
narcissistic psychopaths they camouflage themselves by donating they donate to NGOs
narcisistas se camuflan donando donan a
going animal rights promoting
ong yendo animalistas promulgando
values ​​a very shady face without
valores una cara muy turbia sin
empathy I don't think it has anything to
empatía yo no creo que tenga nada que
do with narcissism I say it right eh I mean I
ver con el narcisismo Lo deigo rejón eh
think it has to do with with
o sea yo creo que tiene que ver con con
with no way out since the time and that's it
con sinen salidad desde la época y punto
Shameless of the time also
Sinvergüenza de la época además
Shameless ally of the
Sinvergüenza aliad de la
time today you go with the look of Jordi Wil it
época hoy vas con el look de Jordi wil
's true we are Look look look look It's
es verdad estamos Mira mira mira mira Es
true that I have Jordi Wild in the background and
verdad que tengo de fondo a Jordi Wild y
and we are here the two most
y estamos aquí los dos canales más
important gossip channels commenting on gossip
importantes del salseo comentando salseo
with with the basketball jerseys
con con las camisetas de basket
it's true it's true I did it without
es verdad es verdad lo he hecho sin
wanting to I did it without wanting to things we
querer lo he hecho sin querer cosas lo
carry it inside we carry it
llevamos en el interior lo llevamos en
inside
interior
Ah how heavy this has been eh how heavy
Ah qué heavy esto ha sido eh qué heavy
this has been
ha sido esto
eh They published here today in
eh Por aquí han publicado hoy en el
Spanish an interview with Carlota
español una entrevista a Carlota
Corredera that I'm going to expand because I don't feel like
corredera que la voy a ampliar porque no
breaking my eyes there and I'm
tengo ganas de dejarme la vista ahí y os
going to read it to you okay I took it in the
la voy a leer vale me he llevado en el
no in Spanish  in Spanish, [ __ ]
no en el español en el español [__]
How did they remove Carlota Corredera from
Cómo quitaron a Carlota corredera de la
TV,
tele
eh How did they remove her,
eh Cómo la quitaron
eh How did they remove her, eh How do they, eh, was
eh Cómo la quitaron eh Cómo se se se
her image buried, eh, does it seem that
enterró su imagen eh os parece para
much to you, really, yes, no. I mean, it causes
tanto en realidad sí no O sea causa
a lot of rejection, no, but as much as over
muchísimo rechazo no pero tanto como
there, the media banishment, man, I
para allá el el destierro mediático tío
mean because in the end, but it's that
o sea porque al final ya pero es que
nobody, nobody wants to watch a program that
nadie nadie quiere ver un programa que
presents her,
lo presente ella
no, fat, traitor, you put it out
no gorda traicionera ponéis por
there, how strong, eh How, how did they remove her,
ahí qué fuerte eh Cómo cómo la quitaron
eh, from having a powerful position to outside, eh,
eh de tener un cargo potente a fuera eh
nothing,
nada
eh I've had few surprises, I know
eh Me he llevado pocas sorpresas yo sé
who I can count on And who I can't,
con quién puedo contar Y con quién no
with the people I believed in and I think I'm going to
con la gente que creía y creo que voy a
have a relationship, they're always there, with
tener relación siempre siguen ahí con
those who I had the most doubts about that
quienes tenía más dudas de esa
continuity, well, they're not there. I mean, people, of
continuidad pues no están O sea la gente
course, you're no longer in the media, they ignore
ya Claro ya no estás en el medio ya
you. No, my stage in Sálvame
pasan de ti No mi etapa en sálvame
professionally is closed, man. Of course, my
profesionalmente está cerrada hombre
heart, of course, it's closed, it no longer
Claro corazón claro que está cerrada ya
exists, in my mind, to this day,
existe por mi mente a día de hoy no pasa
returning with them is not possible, neither on a
el volver con ellos ni en una cadena
general channel nor on the one they're on now, we
generalista ni en la que están ahora
have to learn to turn the page. Well,
hay que aprender a pasar página Bueno
but I don't think this has been the case
pero yo creo que esto no ha sido
either.  her decision no I mean they haven't
tampoco decisión de ella no O sea no la
called her to work on it or if we were
han llamado para trabajar en ni que
going No that has been something like a
fuéramos No eso ha sido cosa como
forced vacation no Hey what's going on
muy vacaciones obligadas no Oye qué pasa
we're not going to reach 2000 members I never
no vamos a llegar a 2000 miembros nunca
ask
pregunto
eh the kid well I'll see if I go to the
eh el chisco pues Ya veré si voy a la
salsería today The truth is I have
salsería hoy La verdad es que tengo por
a live prepared around here But I'm a
aquí un directo preparado Pero tengo un
little sleepy I
poco de sueño
mean I have to take a shower and
O sea me tengo que pegar un duchazo y
when I take a shower I'm going to
cuando me pegue un duchazo me voy a
be
quedar
fuf but but if the
fuf pero pero si la
gentlemen 2000 members today we reached
señoreros 2000 miembros hoy llegamos a
2000 members I think you're going to
2000 miembros Me parece que os vaya
stay there
quedar ahí
eh she went to Anne and Lili comes in man of
eh se fue al Anne y entra Lili hombre
course shameless shameless
claro
not tesa
descarados descarados no tesa
But you left the live scheduled already
Pero has dejado el directo programado ya
but well my programming is like
pero bueno mis programaciones son de
that but besides I can
aquella manera pero aparte yo puedo
do whatever I want even if I
hacer lo que quiera aunque lo
program it at the salsería if it has 2000
programe en la salsería si tiene 2000
members man the salsería is 2000 of us
miembros hombre la salsería somos 2000 y
no I don't know how many we are right now
pico no no sé cuántos somos ahora mismo
the salseria be 2500 or
las sal ser 2500 o
3000 How many members are there ampari there are
3000 Cuántos miembros hay ampari hay
approximately 10000
aproximadamente
we are  disappearing little by
estamos desapareciendo poco a
little for me it's very healthy to explore
poco para mí es muy sano el el explorar
other worlds and always stay with them
otros mundos y quedarme siempre con lo
but of course you are exploring other worlds
pero claro que otros mundos estás
Carlota
explorando Carlota
exploring other worlds but if you did
explorar otros mundos pero si has hecho
the podcast and the videos had 2000 views it
lo del podcast y tenían 2000 visitas los
's a door that was closed and I
vídeos es una puerta que se cerró y que
think it shouldn't open again
creo que tampoco debe volver a abrirse
but the door was closed to you
pero es que la puerta te la cerraron
Carlota I don't know I mean I think
Carlota no sé o sea yo creo que todo el
everyone deserves a second
mundo también merece un poco una segunda
chance too eh I'm also
oportunidad eh También te
telling you I mean it's very very very very
digo o sea es muy muy muy
what description would we give it that isn't
qué qué descripción le pondríamos que no
disrespectful or rather
sea una falta de respeto o sea la
Carlota's attitude generated a lot of
actitud de Carlota generaba muchísimo
rejection the
rechazo la
truth but both there and for them to have
verdad pero tanto ahí como para que le
the gate closed on her guy like that
hayan cerrado el portón tío así de en
Seco is exploring the world of unemployment no no Of
Seco está explorando el mundo del paro
course he doesn't say no no it's not that
no no Claro es que no dice no no es que
I'm exploring the world but if you're not
estoy explorando mundo pero si no estás
in any
en nada
media I tried the podcast thing that I would
mediático intentó lo del podcast que ahí
invest in because that podcast was made with
invertiría porque ese posca lo hizo con
a certain quality that had a certain
cierta calidad eso tenía cierta
investment In fact I was trying to
inversión De hecho yo estuve intentando
rent a place to do a debate
alquilar un local para hacer un debate
on the main channel with two
en en el canal principal con dos
guests and such a nice place and it
invitadas y tal aí un sitio bonito y
costs money to have a place like that  eh she
cuesta dinero tener un sitio así eh
closed it herself from her iPhone How do you
se lo cerró ella misma desde iPhone Cómo
give away members Look out there are
se regalan los miembros Mira por ahí hay
people who want to give away members let's
gente que quiere regalar los miembros a
see I think I'm serious now
ver yo creo que ya os lo digo en serio
eh it makes me a little sad telesalseo Eh it
eh me da un poco de pena telesalseo Eh
makes me a little sad telesalseo eh we're
me da un poco de pena telesalseo eh lo
going to fight for it for a few more months but it
vamos a pelear unos meses más pero me
's making me a little sad
está dando un poco de pena
eh It's not, it's not working out
eh No está no está resultando
eh they're overtaking us on the
eh nos están adelantando por la
left all
izquierda
the way to Lolly Huerta today we're going to see
hasta la Lolly Huerta hoy vamos a ver
moñe illo too no Look there María
moñe illo también no Mira por ahí María
Jesús has given us five members a
Jesús nos ha regalado cinco miembros un
kiss
beso
beautiful It's your fault Javi you destroyed
guapa Por tu culpa Javi tú la destruiste
Carlota or telesalseo she
a Carlota o a telesalseo
thought she was above good
se creía que estaba por encima del bien
and man Let's see yes but so much that she
y del man A ver sí pero para tanto como
can't work in a
para que ya no pueda trabajar más en un
medium anymore I don't know it seems very thick no I mean
medio no sé me parece muy tocho no O sea
no he hasn't done like something so
no no ha hecho como algo tan
No he hasn't done like something so so so
No no ha hecho como algo tan tan tan
no Javi you abandoned us but we're
no Javi tú nos abandonaste pero ya hemos
back Alicia queen But we're
vuelto Alicia reina Pero ya hemos
back I haven't been on
vuelto llevo sin salir en la tele
mainstream television for more than 2
generalista más de 2
years I've stopped in a
años he parado en una situación de
privileged situation because I can really still
privilegio porque realmente todavía
choose the jobs  what do I want to
puedo elegir los trabajos que quiero
do or
hacer o
not Carlota Corredera collaborates on a
no Carlota corredera colabora en un
radio program on Spanish radio and television
programa de radio en radio televisión
yes And how come we never
española sí Y cómo es que nunca nos
get any headlines about her what are they
llega ningún titular de ella de qué
talking about What is the program about
hablan De qué trata el programa
what what Currently I am on the
de qué de qué Actualmente estoy en las
afternoons of Radio Nacional de España with
tardes de Radio Nacional de España con
Lourdes Maldonado but I would love to
Lourdes Maldonado pero me encantaría
return to television sooner rather than
volver a la televisión más pronto que
later in the
tarde en la
production company that I have with my husband
productora que tengo con mi marido
we are preparing a documentary about an
estamos preparando un documental sobre
orphan of gender violence Oh if you are
huérfano de violencia de género Ay si
going to be lazy
vas a dar pereza
Carlota if you are going to continue with your stories you
Carlota si vas a seguir con tus cuentos
should present the weather on the radio
debe presentar el tiempo en la radio
Because if it's that we haven't no no I don't
Porque si es que no nos hemos no no no
know it's been 1 year since we haven't received anything from
sé hace 1 que no nos llega nada de de
Carlota Corredera
Carlota corredera
no it's been a million since we received anything
no hace un millón que no nos llega nada
from Carlota
de Carlota
Corredera I understand that it won't be treated
corredera entiendo que no estará tratá
from the heart because if she were doing
de corazón porque si estuviera haciendo
things from the heart they wouldn't
cosas en el corazón no nos
reach us tesa how are we going I'm going to take
llegarían tesa cómo vamos me voy a tomar
the proteins kid I am I am
las proteínas chaval
doing here an
estoy estoy estoy haciendo aquí un
athlete eh it's a discussion on
deportista eh es una tertulia de tema de
current topics but when we talk about
actualidad pero cuando hablamos de de
current topics man my tesa has
tema de actual hombre mi tesa ha
given away 10 but tesa is that it's not worth it it's not
regalado 10 pero tesa es que no vale no
worth it I think that telesalaseo
vale Yo creo que telesalseo
tesa it  we're going to have to close
tesa lo vamos a tener que cerrar
eh How was it I was I'm not
eh Cómo era lo que estaba yo no me
leaving telesalseo we are having a second
voyar telesalseo estamos una segunda
chance but it seems to me
oportunidad pero me parece a mí
that it's going to be the
que va a ser la fábrica de la
tele2 factory better that almost nothing comes from
tele2 mejor que no llegue casi nada de
it for the nonsense that it says man
ella para las tonterías que dice hombre
but let's see if if you are interviewed or
pero a ver si si tú estás entrevistado o
so when I was doing the podcast for example
sea cuando hacía el podcast por ejemplo
when I was doing the podcast we did
cuando hacía el podcast sí que nos
get it and we saw some statement that
llegaba y veíamos alguna declaración que
Patiño had given in I don't know where you
había dado Patiño en no sé dónde
know yes yuki we are giving it a
sabes sí yuki le estamos dando una
second chance telesalseo
segunda oportunidad telesalseo
but it's costing eh that the
pero está costando eh que la
people that the people come back to support you
gente que la gente vuelva a apoyarte
eles salseo
eles salseo
eh I think so and your efforts for
eh yo creo que sí y tus esfuerzos para
salsería and
salsería y
main of course
principal claro
exactly exactly tesa but oh well
exactamente exactamente tesa pero bueno
Let's try Let's try for a
Vamos a intentarlo Vamos a intentarlo un
while
tiempecillo
we are giving it our all
nosotros lo estamos dando todo
eh Mia MIA my
eh Mia MIA
bicep just grew a
me acaba de crecer el bicep una
ton with this
barbaridad con este
shake says Dorina Javi how can you
batido dice dorina Javi cómo podés
always insult a woman I am
insultar siempre una mujer yo estoy
fed up with the insults and the violence
harta de los insultos y de la violencia
of men towards women and nobody
de los hombres hacia las mujeres y nadie
respects them every day it gets worse And I see them
les respeta cada día es peor Y los veo
day after day and nobody does anything Dorina but
día a día y nadie hace nada dorina pero
Who has insulted  to nobody now if
Quién ha insultado a nadie ahora si
I'm here half half
estoy aquí medio medio
asleep says aini it was more complicated to
dormido dice aini era más complicado
revive Javi Oliveira and there he is no there he
revivir Javi oliveira y ahí está no ahí
is Javi Oliveira
está Javi oliveira
Not breaking molds no [ __ ] let's do
No partiendo moldes no [__] vamos a
something we are preparing a
hacer una cosa estamos preparando un
project for Javi Oliveira
proyecto para Javi oliveira
buf buf I'll
buf buf
tell you it's true Lili Lili works in
contaré es verdad Lili Lili trabaja en
television Lili works in telesalseo yes yes
teles Lili trabaja en telesalseo si si
we have to close it Lili I know on the
lo tenemos que cerrar Lili se que en la
street Look over there Monse is going to rescue
calle Mira por ahí Monse va a rescatar
telesalseo family Look monce monce
telesalseo familia Mira monce monce
thank you very much Lili thank
muchas gracias Lili dale las gracias a
Monse
Monse
Javi Set all the members at 0.99 and that way
Javi Pon todos los miembros a 0,99 y así
people will get encouraged you know what happens to
gente es que sabes qué pasa que para
do that yes if I do that I have to
hacer eso si si yo hago eso tengo que
eliminate the other
eliminar las otras
categories and you know what happens when I
categorías y sabéis qué pasa que al
categories that money from all the
categorías ese dinero de todos los
subscribers that I have in the other
suscriptores que yo tenga en las otras
categories they take it away I mean they
categorías me lo quitan O sea me lo
charge me And then well I don't know how to
cobran Y entonces pues no sé cómo
do it but you have three
hacerlo pero ustedes tenéis ahí tres
prices there take the one you
precios [__] el que más os
like the most Look over there our Joe has
guste Mira por ahí nuestro Joe ha
given away another 10 do you want to save the
regalado otros 10 quieres salvarte el
salseo Joe u Joe Joe you sent me one
salseo Joe u Joe Joe me mandaste una
thing and I haven't seen it man What a
cosa y no lo he visto tío Qué
shame Jo I have to see it eh I
sinvergüenza Jo lo tengo que ver eh lo
have to see it I
tengo que ver Te lo
promise you I promise you that this
prometo Te lo prometo que este fin de
weekend I'll find a gap and
semana Busco un hueco y lo
read it It's that my WhatsApp It's a party eh
leo Es que mi WhatsApp Es una fiesta eh
my wasa is a [ __ ]
mi wasa es una [__]
party Javi It's not worth it There are many of us
fiesta Javi No vale la pena Somos muchos
in the other categories No but if it's not that it's not
en las otras categorías No pero si no es
worth it tesa but I don't
que no valga la pena tesa sino que no
feel like they deduct from me Well I don't
tengo ganas de que me descuenten Pues no
know how much money they take from my
sé cuánto dinero que me lo quiten de la
account because they charge you you know I don't know
cuenta porque te lo cobran sabes no sé
why they do it like that because what they
por qué lo hacen así porque lo que
should do when you eliminate a
deberían hacer cuando tú eliminas una
category would be to not renew the
categoría sería pues no renovar más a la
people who are in there anymore you
gente que está ahí dentro me
understand Not that they charge you no that they
entiendes No que te lo no que te lo
charge you and you have to pay it you know I don't
cobren y tengas tú que pagarlo sabes no
know it's a little weird but
sé es un poco raro pero
well it's true what melanina says if we
bueno es verdad lo que dice melanina si
close telesalseo
cerramos telesalseo
no but they would look for scratching the
no pero ya buscarían de rascado del
main one and the salsería Or my
principal y de la salsería O de mi
Twitter or what I said three months ago
Twitter o de lo que dije hace tres meses
that the harassers would be out of
que los acosadores se quedarían sin
work they say out there no Only
trabajo dicen por ahí no Solo
us manoli Montoya says  Javi Don't even think
nosotros manoli Montoya dice Javi Ni se
about closing this channel, let's see, Manoli,
te ocurra cerrar este canal a ver manoli
eh It's not that it would occur to me, but if things don't
eh No es que se me ocurra pero si la
pick up, I have to focus more on,
levanta me tengo que centrar más en
I'm running the three channels right now
estoy llevando los tres canales ahora
and I'm at full capacity, but it's
mismo y estoy a tope pero sí que es
true that man,
verdad que hombre
mm this one is a little down, eh, I mean, I'm
mm este está un poco decaído eh o sea
going to, I'm going to fight it, let's try to get it
voy a voy a pelearlo vamos a intentar
back on, okay. But I see that
levantarlo vale Pero si veo que que la
people are not very keen on the idea of
gente tampoco está muy por la la voz de
getting this telesalseo back on, let's leave it.
que levantemos esto telesalseo lo
That's true, star, they are faithful, yes, they
Eso sí es verdad estrella son fieles sí
are
son
faithful, if we leave t salseo, it will float.
fieles si dejamos t salseo saldrá flote
Javi Gaming, no, no,
Javi Gaming no no
no, if we close telesalseo, we go back to what we've had
no si cerramos telesalseo volvemos a lo
all our lives, the
que hemos tenido toda la vida el
main and the
principal y el
secondary. Well, let's see some fun,
secundario Bueno vamos a ver moñe
while this one. Here, let's see some fun,
mientras que este Aquí vamos a ver moñe
illo Alicia, but you're stretching my
illo Alicia pero me estás estirando
ear too much, says Alicia. But how are
mucho de la oreja dice Alicia Pero cómo
you going to get it back on if you didn't appear,
lo vas a levantar si no aparecías
creature, let's see, Alicia, the summer has been
criatura a ver Alicia el verano ha sido
a bit of a street, but since
un poco de calle manera pero desde que
we came back
hemos vuelto en desde que hemos vuelto
after the
después de
summer, we're at full capacity, eh, we're at full capacity
verano estamos a tope eh estamos a tope
every day following content, eh
todos los días siguiendo contenido eh
uploading content and creating it.  as much as
subiendo contenido y creando lo mejor
possible in the live shows I think we're
posible sea en los directos yo creo que
giving it our all eh
lo estamos dando todo eh
I think that in the live shows I feel
yo creo que en los directos me me da
really sorry for some of the live shows we
mucha pena alguno de los directos que
're doing because the
estamos haciendo porque los
live shows are brutal they're brutal and
directos son brutales son brutales y no
we're not getting responses But well we're
estamos teniendo respuestas Pero bueno
going to fight it eh I'm trying for a
lo vamos a pelear eh lo voy intentado un
couple more months and and I trust I trust
par de meses más y y yo confío confío en
that with leaving us there You know
que con con dejarnos ahí
I think that by working hard he'll get back on his feet
Sabes Yo creo que currando se vuelve a
then the little house then what will happen with the
pues la casito pues qué pasará con el
show with Marina because man if it does
programa con Marina porque hombre que si
n't work No what can I tell you well like
no funciona No qué te digo pues como
everything
todo
No well no Lili Lili I can say what you
No pues no Lili Lili puedo decir lo que
wrote to me but the thing is I don't agree
escrito pero es que no estoy de acuerdo
because it doesn't matter it wouldn't matter the
porque da igual daría igual los
stalkers let's see Lili tells me that the
acosadores a ver me dice Lili que los
stalkers
acosadores
eh if we close this they'll die it's
eh que si cerramos esto que se mueren es
like no because they would pull out
como no porque ellos ya tirarían de
anything from Javi but if they talk about
cualquier cosa de Javi pero si hablan de
Javi even if it's just any
Javi aunque sea de cualquier
tweet a kiss a kiss TT Well let's
tweet un beso un beso TT Bueno vamos a
see a little bun
ver un poco de moño
no let's see a little bun No
no vamos a ver un poco de moño
that's true sus That's true
No eso sí es verdad sus Eso sí es verdad
sus But you know what happens of course the
sus Pero sabéis qué pasa que claro el
Sancho issue  I took it for the beginning
tema Sancho me lo llevé para princip
because in reality it had to have
porque en realidad tuvo que haber estado
always been there then whether you like it or not it is
ahí siempre entonces quieras que no es
content that is there not here it is
un contenido que está allí no aquí es
that my main channel is Jai Oliveira
que mi canal principal es Jai oliveira
telesalseo it is the third
telesalseo es el tercero
eh well manoli we are going to try
Eh bueno manoli lo vamos a intentar
manoli
manoli
Montoya Javi you are from palancas What is
Montoya Javi eres del palancas Qué es el
palancas is it true dolores says Dolores
palancas es verdad dolores dice Dolores
a while ago I wanted to close the
hace un tiempo quería cerrar el canal
main channel and now you see Yes yes
principal y ahora ya ves Sí sí
we will fight dolores we will fight well let's
pelearemos dolores pelearemos bueno a
see I'm not telling you that I'm going to
ver no os estoy diciendo que lo vaya a
close it tomorrow eh I'm telling you that
cerrar mañana eh os estoy diciendo que
we are making several strategies to get it
estamos haciendo varias estrategias para
back up but of course
volver a volver a levantarlo pero claro
if we do
si
n't go
no vamos
no if it doesn't
no si no
go the plaque it's true Estela I have to
va la placa es verdad Estela tengo que
ask for the plaque eh I think we are going to
pedir la placa eh yo creo que nos vamos
leave without a plaque Well let's see bun no no
a ir sin placa Bueno vamos a ver moño no
no start with the mourning because we are not like
no no empecéis con el luto que todavía
that yet we are not at that
no no estamos así no estamos en ese
point Do not start with the
punto No empecéis con el
mourning I would never have known
luto no hubiera conocido nunca
always In order not to see you without seeing you to
siempre Para no verte sin verte para
feel your
sentir tu
memory I'm only going to say one thing I'm not going
recuerdo solo voy a decir una cosa no
to answer no Out of cowardice but in order
voy a contestar no Por cobardía sino por
not to give fodder to the good scavengers
no darle carnaza a los bues carroñeros
that are there on other
que están ahí en otros
channels who has  said that he's not going to
canales a quién le ha dicho que no va a
answer so as not to pester her
contestar para no darle canaza
Who, who is this carrion vulture calling?
A quién a quién está llamando esta
What are we going to do? How do
carroñero Qué vamos a hacer cómo rebes
you say
tú a Palabras
foolish words? You have to turn a deaf ear. No, it
necias tienes que hacer oyos sordos No
's not cowardice. Well,
no es cobardía
there are people who know how to
e Pues si es que hay gente que se sabe
portray themselves, and I'm a little more, I
retratar a sí mismo y yo un poco más
have to look at the coward. Life
tengo que mira mira la cobarde la vida
is a but a total nonsense,
es un pero un despropósito total
so one of two things: either you take it with
entonces una de dos o te lo toma con
humor, they weren't either. They were foolish words
humor tampoco eran eran Palabras necias
to turn a deaf ear. Or you take it with
que hacer oído sordo O te lo tomas con
humor. Loli doesn't answer Loli clearly. Loli
humor a Loli a Loli no le contesta claro
doesn't answer Loli clearly. She
a Loli no le contesta claro a Loli nos
loves us like crazy, but with Loli she has no
quiere [__] pero con Loli no tiene
[ __ ]. eh, not with Loli. eh, let's mess
[__] eh con Loli no eh vamos a meternos
with the guind for one more day. It's not that the
con el guind un día más no es que el
guindy didn't come today. It's that the guindy has been on
guindy hoy no no ha venido Es que es que
vacation for a week. No,
el guindy lleva una semana de vacaci no
no, no, no the guindy, the guindy is my
no no no el gindy el guindy mi
obsession. Loli doesn't want to say anything to
obsesión a Loli no le quiere decir ni
her, but it's
mo pero
always, always been like that. eh, I
siempre pero siempre ha sido así eh o
mean, it was like that at the time.
sea ya fue así en su momento
eh No no Of course it's for Loli if it were me of
eh No no Claro es por Loli si fuera a mí
course man yes to me she's going to continue
claro hombre a mí sí a mí me va a seguir
dedicating her entire life to me that's clear that's
dedicando su vida entera eso está claro
why no one answers Loli
sabemos por qué ninguna contesta Loli
man in Tania's case because Tania
hombre en el caso de Tania porque Tania
what she didn't want was for her to bring up the thing about her
lo que no quería era que sacase lo de su
husband for Loli to say about her husband
marido que Loli dijera lo de su marido
which is as you can see she insinuated it and
que es como ya ves tú lo ha insinuado y
we understood everything perfectly
lo hemos entendido todo perfectamente
but Peppa why is she [ __ ] herself too but I do
pero Peppa por qué se caga también pero
n't know exactly what about Because they've also
no sé exactamente de qué Porque también
said
se han dicho de
everything when I laugh I'm half
todo cuando me río me medio
Toa I'm saying It's that the
Toa estoy diciendo Yo que es que los
scavengers are everywhere
carroñeros están en todos los sitios
But there are scavengers there are people who talk
Pero hay carroñeros hay gente que habla
And well then about what happened yesterday that was
Y bueno pues de lo que pasó ayer que fue
so spectacular So they can
tan espectacular Así que os pueden dar
screw the lady, the son and the
por culo a la señora al hijo y a la
mother But then she's not going to answer about
madre Pero entonces no va a contestar en
returning the money the
devolverle el dinero la
climber is not going to answer about returning the
trepa no va a contestar de devolverle el
money because Loli what was left in it
dinero porque Loli lo que en lo que
lolin who wanted the money
quedó lolin que quería el dinero de
back no
vuelta no
Ah there she doesn't want to
Ah ahí no quiere
answer [ __ ] Peppa with how interesting you
contestar [__] Peppa con lo interesante
were she knows your answer regarding that
que estabas sabe tu respuesta respecto a
give the money back to Loli  that is
eso devuélvele el dinero a Loli que es
disgusting money
un dinero asqueroso
Peppa every time they get angry
Peppa cada vez que se enfadan aparece
a new lap appears mother of God mother of
una vueltas nueva madre de Dios madre de
God
Dios
tesa okay it
tesa vale os da
really pisses you off what a late afternoon we are against it
muchísimo por culo vaya tarde que
scavenger put yourself against
llevamos la contrao carroñero ponte
me every afternoon
mí
come from memberships up down
venir de membresías para arriba para
inside
dentro
out what was going on that she
afuera qué es lo que estaba pasando que
was waiting for me to be
estaba pendiente de que estaba yo en
live because I put myself yesterday
directo porque yo me puse ayer por la
afternoon as if I was
tarde como si yo estuviera
waiting to see if she is or isn't
pendiente de si ella está o no
Ana a kiss gorgeous Look it's
está Ana un beso guapísima Mira se ha
done my Look look look look at
hecho mi Mira mira mira
her but either she was waiting for or rather if I was
mírala pero sea que estaba pendiente de
live you are not
o sea de si estaba yo en directo no
live what viewers did she have While
estás en directo qué espectadores tenía
I was live family or rather if
Estando yo en directo familia o sea si
I put myself live at the same time
yo me pongo en directo a la misma hora
as the climber what weighers does she have left
que la trepa qué pesadores le quedan a
someone Someone saw by chance
ella alguien Alguien vio por casualidad
does Peppa say that yesterday you did
es que Peppa dice que ayer hiciste
live in the afternoon to do counter
directo por la tarde para hacerle contra
programming Yes yes man of course I am
programación Sí sí hombre claro me
very interested in
interesa mucho hacerle la
competing with her nobody looked at who saw who the
competencia nadie le dio por mirar qué
viewers But it would be interesting to see
espectadores Pero sería interesante ver
who the viewers are, let's see since
qué espectadores tiene a ver ya en los
lately she was having 300 400
últimos tiempos estaba teniendo 300 400
well it would be interesting to know what
pues estaría interesante sab qué
viewers  has if I'm
espectadores tiene si estoy yo en
live suddenly in the afternoon 200 200
directo de repente por la tarde 200 200
240 Well look, I didn't want 240 Well there it
240 Pues mira no quería 240 Pues ahí lo
was, listen to me 200 didn't fit and
estuvo escúchame 200 no le quedó y
many would be who would be speaking at the same
muchos serían que estarían hab los la
time, of
vez
course, let's see It's that to see Javi
claro a ver Es que para ve a Javi
Oliveira on the Canal de la Pepa you see him you
oliveira en el Canal de la [__] lo ves
see On his own Of course,
lo ves En el suyo propio
what a late day we have the contradiction
claro vaya tarde que llevamos la contrao
scavenger put yourself every afternoon
carroñero ponte todas las tardes a
against programming
contra programarme a
me in it's a becoming of of of
mí en es un devenir de de de de
memberships up and down what they
membresías para arriba para abajo qué le
were giving him a lot of
estaban dando mucho
money
dinero
Lili that they are giving him a lot of money the
Lili que le están dando mucho dinero la
people this This is like what we were
gente esto Esto es como lo que estábamos
talking about before about that we are
hablando antes del de que somos
idiots I mean there are people who start
[__] O sea hay gente que se pone a
giving money to this one with what he has
darle dinero a esta con lo que ha
done 221 had today with the
hecho 221 tenía hoy con el
space 200 viewers little ones it's still a
space 200 espectador cillos todavía es
lot eh it's still a lot eh And you still
mucho eh todavía es mucho eh Y todavía
know what still that little is for
sabéis qué todavía ese poco es por
me to see Oliveira on any
mí para ver a oliveira en cualquier
channel I see him I see him on his Of course I
canal lo veo lo veo en el suyo Claro que
hear him man Monica a kiss
lo lo oigo hombre Mónica un beso
Thank you very much
Muchísimas gracias
beautiful Sure
guapa
sure but still the 200 still the
claro pero todavía los 200 todavía los
is a lot what the [ __ ] watch this I mean
es mucho qué [__] ve esto O sea
imagine sitting down and watching
imagínate sentarte a ve
this but but still those 200 are for
esto pero pero todavía esos 200 son por
me pata
mí pada
spañ but not to m a d they have to already I do
españ pero no a m a d tienen que ya va
n't know why it wasn't
No sé por qué no se renovó
automatically renewed okay okay We forgive you
automáticamente vale vale Te perdonamos
anusca we forgive you welcome back in
anusca te perdonamos bienvenida de
out Jai Jai Jai
nuevo para dentro a fuera Jai Jai Jai
Jai Oh it creeps me out that he says my name
Jai Ay qu grima me da que diga mi nombre
all [ __ ] day really I mean no no no
todo el [__] día de verdad O sea
no today who
que que no que no que no hoy quién me lo
told me I don't remember who a friend
decía no me acuerdo quién una amiga me
told me dude she's already a lady Every
decía tío es que ya es una señora Todos
[ __ ] day dedicating herself to you Every
los [__] días dedicándose a ti Todos
[ __ ] day harassing a person the
los [__] días acosando a una persona a
same person
la misma persona
eh when you're already asking her to stop to leave
eh cuando se le está pidiendo ya que
you I don't know what And she's a
pare que te deje que no sé qué Y es una
very person, I mean it's weird it's weird
persona muy o sea es raro es raro
no to me Javi doesn't give a damn anymore
no a mí Javi ya me la suda un poco
baby he leaves me alone Well you know what I'm
beb ya me deja solo Pues sabes lo que os
telling you, you know what I'm telling you, clueless, I
digo sabes lo que os digo
can't believe it
empanado no me lo puedo creer
[Laughs]
[Risas]
this kid is
este niño es
stupid this kid  He's 40 years old but he's
tonto este niño tiene 40 años pero está
still in his teens and hasn't really
todavía en la edad del pavo sin
woken up. At 41, he goes there
espavilar con 41 años se pone ahí a en
instead of taking the internet away from his mother. Let's say
vez de quitarle a la madre el internet
my mother has it. Well, I was going to
vamos yo mi madre tiene Bueno te iba a
tell you, my mother is 70 years old and she does this.
decir mi madre tiene 70 años y hace esto
No, no, but it doesn't matter. I mean, even if my
no no pero da igual o sea aunque mi
mother were 50, my mother is doing
madre tuviera 50 mi madre está haciendo
the things she does. This lady on the
las cosas que hace Esta señora en
internet, the digital footprint she's
internet la huella digital que le está
leaving on the family, the
dejando a la familia lo de los
240 thing, the shame they've caused by the
240 la vergüenza que han hecho con lo de
240 thing, the shame they've caused by
los 240 la vergüenza que han hecho
scratching Loli, I mean, everything with the
rascando a Loli o sea todo todo lo del
cancer, I mean, I quit and he doesn't [ __ ]. He
cáncer o sea yo quito y él no é coge
comes home from
llega de
work and sits there and of course he sees it
trabajar y se sienta ahí y claro lo ve
like a toy, he's playing at being a
como un juguete está jugando a ser
youtuber. He's 41 years old, the baby is 41
youtuber 41 años la guagüita tiene 41
years old, he has the candy and look what he's
añitos tiene el caramelo y mira lo que
done. It's funny, he takes one of
ha hecho la gracia coge un
mine in which I'm doing something
mío en el que yo estoy haciendo una
stupid on purpose, not to laugh, and
tontería a propósito no para reírnos y
he does it like a joke, a bully. I don't
él lo hace como una burla un bully No
know, I can't
sé no me lo puedo
believe it, he
creer
looks and laughs by himself, the jerk, he's
mira y se ríe el solo el carajote el
alone, the jerk laughing at  the grace
solo el carajote riéndose de la gracia
that has done or rather has stopped to
que ha hecho o sea se ha parado a
download the
descargarse el
video dude has the guys not to [ __ ]
vídeo tío tiene los tios para no cagarse
himself eh
encima eh
Hey hey Thanks so much oh
Oye oye Muchísimas
Hey well look I just received a
ay Oye pues mira me acaba de llegar un
visa but the person won't let me say
visum pero no me deja la persona decir
who it is but thank you very much but thank you very much
quién es pero muchas gracias pero muchas
to that
gracias a esa
person I'm
persona me
freaking out I'm already burned out there okay I'm there I'm already
flipa ya estoy quemado ahí vale Ya estoy
I'm alone as a host we
ya estoy yo solo de anfitrión te damos
welcome you slowly escame pass it by
la bienvenid despacio escame páselo por
md that I put okay it's here the
md que yo ponga vale está aquí el
space you see it here no no but pass it to
espacio lo veis aquí no no pero pásamelo
me by md share it with by md I'm
por md compártelo con por md lo estoy
putting it here mom but by md protect me
poniendo aquí mamá pero por md protégeme
Lord with your
señor con tu
spirit protect me Lord with your
espíritu protégeme señor con tu
spirit the title has put my son
espíritu el título ha puesto mi hijo la
Pepa has suffered a lot
[__] ha sufrido mucho
churra That's the title what they
churra Ese es el título lo que le
put on the
pusieron al
space dude but yours you are sick
space tío pero lo tuyo estás enferma
Peppa You are very sick You are very
Peppa Estás muy enferma Estás muy
sick and your son is that he is a
enferma y tu hijo es que es un una
little sick thing that you are still raising you
cosita malita que estás criando todavía
almost have him at 41 years old that I don't know from
casi lo tienes con 41 años que no s de
the house listen to me open a space on
la casa escúchame abres un space de
Twitter I mean it says that you go  to do
Twitter o sea dice que vas a hacer un
something different one day, Peppa puts on her, she
día una cosa diferente le pone la Peppa
suffered a lot, a reference Javi also, do
sufrió mucho una referencia Javi también
you have a poster of Javi in ​​your house,
tienes póster de Javi en tu casa el en
the magnets he sticks on the fridge are
el frigorífico los imanes que pega son
of Javi, well, it's that we're
de Javi bueno es que que estamos
hallucinating but it's that we're
alucinando pero es que estamos
hallucinating when we're
alucinando cuando
really talking about a lady
realmente estamos hablando de una señora
who on her birthday they put up
que en su cumpleaños le pusieron los
10,500 balloons making fun of her that
globos de 10500 haciendo una burla que
I won 10,500 euros in
yo gané 10500 eur en
cryptocurrency it's an
criptomoneda es una
illness no no but it's not about
enfermedad no no pero no se trata de
shame no shame it's about an
vergüenza no vergüenza se trata de una
illness when they've reached their ceiling no no
enfermedad llegado a su techo no no
when you think they can't humiliate themselves any more they
cuando crees que no se pueden humillar
fall a little further
más tesa caen todavía un poquito más
down they say Wait wait I
para abajo dice Espérate Espérate que lo
can do it I can still do it I can
puedo que lo puedo todavía que lo puedo
still make it
todavía
worse I must stay calm To avoid
empeorar debo mantenerme sereno Para no
falling into madness it's already
caer en la locura ya
late let's see let's see if the pil sends me more
tarde a ver a ver si la pil me manda más
bun let's
muño
see if she doesn't make me explode
ver a ver si no me pone un estall
Antonio we'll see okay because there's a bun
Antonio lo vemos vale porque hay un moño
here
aquí
from there's a bun here from
de hay un moño aquí de
Consuelo
Consuelo
Ah but p Pili sent me here bun
Ah pero p Pili me ha mandado aquí moño
one moment I'm going to the bathroom Eh I won't be long
un momento que voy al baño Eh no tardo
at all
absolutamente
nothing no
nada al
one has left you have waited for me
no se ha ido nadie me habéis esperado
how strong no one has left you have waited for me
qué fuerte no se ha ido nadie me habéis
how
qué
strong we are going to take a walk
fuerte nos vamos a dar una vuelta
do irl or
hacemos irl o
something let's see let's see something by
algo a ver vamos a ver una cosa de
Antonio David to give it context but
Antonio David para darle contexto pero
what happens is that they sent me
lo que pasa es que me han mandado por
here a bun of the pingao Wait Let's see it let's see Let's see let's see let's
aquí un moño del pingao Espérate Vamos a
see This of the
A ver vamos a ver vamos a ver Esto del
loser and now we will see what Antonio does av I'll
pringao y ahora vemos lo de Antonio av
tell you what happened
os lo comento lo que ha pasado que ha
something happened
pasado una
said Guadalupe I thought that you had
cosa dicho Guadalupe pensaba que te
gone to Mexico over there there are fewer
había a México por ahí hay menos
views the
visualizaciones ya se fueron los
slum dwellers already left Ah why aren't we talking
villeros Ah porque no estamos hablando
about the
de de la
people here I say right now the lady
gente aquí yo digo ahora mismo la señora
from the south or Loli Huerta and again no son
del sur o Loli Huerta y otra vez no hijo
nocho we are going to be calm
nocho vamos a estar tranquilo
Although we are going to talk about Javier Oliveira
Aunque vamos a hablar de Javier oliveira
and all these people in case you want to come in
y toda esta gente por si queré entrando
or whatever Or whatever let's see they are all the same man they
o sea O sea a ver todos iguales tío se
[ __ ] on each other a lot and
cagan entre ellos muchas veces y y
with me they are sick man I mean they
conmigo están enfermos tío O sea a mí me
consider me as a
consideran como una
person they consider me as a
persona a mí me consideran como una
dehumanized person I mean we
persona deshumanizada o sea de mí se
can talk about me Okay says Oh look there were
puede hablar Vale dice Ay mira había
a lot of people in my live and already  there is no they have
mucha gente en mi directo y ya no la hay
left Well they have left because
se han ido Bueno pues se han ido porque
today we are not going to talk about the people right now
hoy no vamos a haar de la gente yo ahora
this This is something like they
mismo esto Esto es una cosa como que lo
repeat it a lot No no no yes right now
repiten mucho No no no si yo ahora mismo
I start talking about Peppa and this we have
me pongo a hablar de la Peppa y de esto
25000 people here let's
vamos tengo aquí 25000 personas vamos a
see and then they have 400
ver y luego tienen 400
m says no no yes right now I talk about
m dice no no si yo ahora mismo hablo de
Peppa and about the no how did the
la Peppa y de la no cómo lo ha dicho la
lady from the south and the other one say Okay now
señora del sur y la otra Bueno ahora
the people come again Calm down
viene la gente de nuevo Tranquilo
calm down I'm not going to talk about her
tranquilo que no voy a hablar de ell
but I'm going to talk about jav oliveira okay it
pero voy a hablar de jav oliveira vale
's like dude let me go already guys let me go now you're
es como tío soltarme ya cabrones
going to erase my
soltarme ya que me vais a borrar los
tattoos you have me holding my
tatuajes que me tenéis agarrando el
arm so tight now you're going to erase my
brazo tan fuerte ya que me vais a borrar
tattoos I told Guadalupe I thought I had
tatuajes me dicho Guadalupe pensaba que
you I go to Mexico over there broken there are
te había I a México por ahí brado hay
fewer views the
menos visualizaciones ya se fueron los
slum dwellers already left Ah why aren't we talking
villeros Ah porque no estamos hablando
about the
de de la
people here I say right now the lady
gente aquí yo digo ahora mismo la señora
from the south or Lolly Huerta and again well
del sur o Lolly Huerta y otra vez bueno
No son no apart goes we're going to be
No hijo no aparte va vamos a estar
calm
tranquilos
Although we're going to talk about Javier oliveira
Aunque vamos a hablar de Javier oliveira
and all these people  in case you want to
y toda esta gente por si queréis
come in and get a seat quietly because I
entrando y cogiendo sitio tranquilos que
also have a few clicks for those people there.
también tengo para esa gente ahí unos
Good job if Filemón talks, let's see
cuantos clicks buen dej si habla el
what the [ __ ] is he
ver pero qué [__] es lo que se pone a
talking about
habla de
me, what is he talking about me about
mí qué se pone a hablar de mí de lo de
Serene Javi the wig and these things
serene Javi el peluca y estas cosas
wig yours
peluca la tuya
Mortadelo let's see what that
mortadelo a ver que lo que dice el
loser says about me, you whistle what he
pringado hecho de mí se pite tú lo que
starts watching eh eh the loser br
se pone a ver eh eh el pringado br no
has no other name than a loser But
tiene otro nombre que un pringado Pero
how are you going to watch this when
cómo te vas a poner a ver esto cuando
you have Loli Huerta [ __ ] on your
tienes a la Loli Huerta cagándose en la
pppa and telling him to give her the
pppa y diciéndole que le devuelva el
money back,
dinero
loser and and they are splashing you, they
pringado y y están salpicando te a ti te
are putting you in the middle all day long
están metiendo por por medio todo el día
saying that you were I mean, you know about
diciendo que tú fuiste O sea tú sabes lo
the 240, you exposed it, about the cancer of the one who
de los 240 lo expusiste tú lo del cáncer
doesn't have it but doesn't have it, I mean,
del que no tiene pero no tiene o sea
eh Javi, eight channels join together
eh Javi que se unen ocho canales a
every day to talk about you, they are pathetic
diario para hablar de ti son penosos
Europe, but it's that I have eight, I don't
Europa pero es que se Tengo ocho no
have 15 channels talking about me every day, I
tengo 15 canales hablando de mí al día
counted them.  another day okay one day there were
los conté el otro día vale un día hubo
15 channels talking about me
15 canales hablando de mí
in some of them with various extracts
em algunos de ellos con varios extractos
also okay And then the ones that agreed that we should
además vale Y luego los que quedo en que
n't talk about each other they
no hablemos los unos de los otros te
throw a barb at you or they keep mentioning you or they
tiran pua o o te siguen mencionando o
talk about everything that's
hablan de todo lo que está a tu
around you all the time it's like I have to
alrededor todo el tiempo es como que
[ __ ] with you to see if he catches me Hey my brand of
[__] a ver si me coge Eh mi marca de
deodorant and he pays me for the promotion
desodorante y me paga por la promoción
because don't see Hey don't see how addictive
porque no veas Eh no vea como engancha
the deodorant that I
el desodorante que me que me he
made is, we can see it eh Look I mean it's
hecho lo podemos ver eh Mira O sea que
not something that I invented
no es una cosa que yo me invente
man my trium can come on this is my
hombre mi trium puede vamos este es mi
trium thank goodness okay Javi Oliveira
trium menos mal vale Javi oliveira
spreads fake and they catch him for Oh my god
difunde fake y le pillan para Ay la
this guy this guy
madre que me parió este tío este tío
mother of the mother beautiful this guy who
madre de la madre hermoso este tío que
This is another one oh oh how is this one
Este es otro uy uy u cómo está este u
how is he but this one speaks with such
cómo está pero este habla con una
envy and with one thing don't look at Javi
envidia y con una cosa no veáis a Javi
please they catch him in a fake for a change
por favor le pillan un fake para variar
but my God but if they keep confirming
pero Dios mío pero si se van confirmando
every day all the exclusives that I
cada día to todas las exclusivas que
say Oh oh but it's not even worth paying
digo Ay Ay pero si es que no es ni para
attention to  my mother and has to
echarle cuenta madre mía y tiene que
eat you have to eat from me
comer tienes que comer de mí
your son my son So you invented
tú hijo mío O sea que que te inventaste
a judge you invented I don't know what you
una jueza te inventaste no sé qué te
invented I don't know how much Oh my mother who
inventaste no sé cuánto Ay la madre que
gave birth to me what the mother who gave birth to me You
me parió que la madre que me parió Es
know what happens they play the role that they have
que sabes qué pasa que hacen el papel de
the role or or they carry the role that they hate
que tienen el rol o o llevan el rol de
Javi Oliveira but they
que odian a Javi oliveira pero les
would love that Javi Oliveira look look
encantaría ese Javi oliveira mira mira
Javi Oliveira betrays Dallas and together
Javi oliveira traiciona a Dallas y junto
with his colleague they expose an edited photo they
a su colega exponen una foto editada me
trolled me I put Maricel and Javi Olive in their place
trolearon pongo en su sitio a maricel y
Oh really But this what
a Javi Olive Ay de verdad Pero esto qué
this is that I really I mean Eh This is
esto es que yo de verdad O sea Eh Esto
tremendous Eh This
es tremendo
is tremendous Eh yes let's see what
Eh Esto es tremendo Eh sí a ver lo de
this man is doing I'm not going to tell you what it is
este señor no os voy a decir lo que es
because this man is going to have several
porque este señor va a tener varias
lawsuits
demandas
So I can't tell you what I
Entonces no puedo deciros lo que
really think about what he does But
realmente pienso de lo que hace Pero
well I think it's more than obvious it's not
bueno Yo creo que es más que obvio no es
a bit like the pppa
un poco como la pppa
in Javi Oliveira Javi Oliveira Explains
em Javi oliveira Javi oliveira Explica
how Auro's mother fell into the bite
cómo cayó en el bite la madre de Auro
Javi
expone Javi
Oliveira exposes fake news Oh well about
oliveira noticia falsa Ay pues sobre lo
the  I'm going to tell you something about the beating he's
de del os voy a comentar algo la paliza
taking what a beating I'm
que se está llevando qué paliza me estoy
taking
llevando
but if he started collaborating with
yo pero si se puso a colaborar con la
Peppa because she criticizes you Yeah yeah but the
Peppa porque te critica Sí sí pero lo de
240 thing that's it was okay
los 240 eso de la eso no pasaba nada
right to collaborate with someone who
verdad para colaborar con alguien que ha
did the 240 thing no Lili Javi
hecho lo de los 240 no Lili Javi
Oliveira upset with his stutter But if I have
oliveira molesto con tartaja Pero si yo
n't said anything but if I haven't
no he dicho nada pero si no le he
answered him the mother who
contestado la madre que me
gave birth to me Javi Oliveira explodes against the
parió Javi oliveira explota contra la
Uncle
tertulia del tío
Sur chat show he's a
Sur es un
traitor explodes against his biggest
traidor explota en contra de su mayor
hater and who would be the
hater y cuál sería el
biggest gibel reacts to Javi
mayor gibel reacciona al lores de Javi
Oliveira's lords gibel reacts Javi Oliveira
oliveira gibel reacciona Javi oliveira
exposing Gemita Fran remembers the
exponiendo a gemita Fran se acuerda del
envious jav
envidioso jav
Oliveira
oliveira
Oh Javi Oliveira but this man What is it that he
Ay Javi oliveira pero este señor Qué es
has what's
lo que tiene qué es lo que le
wrong with him I mean with all the topics there are eh No no
pasa o sea con la de temas que hay eh No
Javi Javi Javi my or what I want to do
no Javi Javi Javi mi o lo que yo quiero
stand here to see what Javi does
hacer ponerme aquí a ver qué hace Javi
if Javi doesn't do anything then Javi No
si Javi no hace nada pues Javi No
tremendous pullita Javi
tremenda pullita Javi
Oliveira perma
oliveira perma
[Music]
[Música]
bam  the mother who me jav oliveira gemita
bam la madre que me jav oliveira gemita
dasas
dasas
nim is a
nim es un
dog Argos is Javi
perro Argos es Javi
jav oliveira
jav oliveira
banned Look at Ricky Ed eating Javi
baneado Mira Ricky Ed papeando Javi
oliveira But when that happened man it's
oliveira Pero eso cuando pasó tío es
tremendous
tremendo
[Music]
[Música]
eh it's tremendous tremendous tremendous no but
eh es tremendo tremendo tremendo no pero
now I'm noticing things a little
ahora estoy notando la cosa un poco más
calmer eh I mean I see it a little
calmada eh o sea lo veo un poco más
calmer
calmado
eh I see it I see it a little calmer
eh lo veo lo veo un poco más calmado
eh Javi d all the no no no
eh Javi d todo el no no no
Javi oliveira against cristob bru and I
Javi oliveira contra cristob bru y yo
but How many channels at the end of the day eh
pero Cuántos canales al cabo del día eh
suor your worst opinion out of
suor su peor opinión sobre
eight what did I
ocho qué
say the talk show responds to Javi
dije la tertulia responde a Javi
oliveira for the accusation of
oliveira por la acusación de
plagiarism
plagio
What do they give him with everything everyone gives Javi
What le dan con todo todos le dan a Javi
oliveira
oliveira
Oh if Javi olira left if Ja olira
Ay si Javi olira se fuera si Ja olira se
left mind with a two-year sentence two
fuera mente con dos años de condena dos
years scraped you wouldn't go to jail
años raspados tú no entraba en la cárcel
and the first person who has gone to
y la primera persona que ha entrado en
jail with a two-year sentence has
la cárcel con dos años de condena ha
been Isabel Pantoja But because it was an
sido Isabel Pantoja Pero porque fue un
exemplary punishment exemplary punishment ificant it is
ejemplar castigo ejemplar ficante se
said yes she was the only one with two
dice sí fue la única con dos
years two years of sentence has been Isabel
años dos años de condena ha sido Isabel
Pantoja but let's see the normal thing with if it
Pantoja pero a ver lo normal con si si
is less than 2 years and one day the normal thing
son menos de 2 años y un día lo normal
is that you can request a suspension of
es que pueda solicitar la suspensión de
sentence okay to request a suspension
pena vale para solicitar la suspensión
of sentence you have to pay everything that is
de pena tienes que pagar todo lo que sea
the civil part of what you
la parte civil de de la de lo que te
have been sentenced for okay take charge of the
hayan condenado vale hacerte cargo de la
civil liability not have a
responsabilidad civil no tener
criminal record not have accumulated
antecedentes penales no haber acumulado
more sentences Okay then Isabel Pantoja
más penas Vale entonces Isabel Pantoja
Well let's see yes
Pues a ver sí
exemplary Well of course but it's that the the the
ejemplarizante Bueno claro pero es que
money
el el el el money
Oh my God because it was an
Ay Dios mío porque fue un castigo
exemplary punishment exemplary punishment exemplary it is
ejemplar castigo ejemplar ficante se
said yes she was the only one with two years she has to
dice sí fue la única con dos años tiene
normally to go to jail you have to
que normalmente para que entre la cárcel
put in two years and one day
tien que ponerte a dos años y un día
well let's go with Mr. Oliveira let's see if we can
bueno vamos con señor oliveira a ver si
raise the bill now as in the
subimos la billera ya como para el caso
Pantoja case it is not interesting then we go with
Pantoja no interesa pues nos vamos con
Javier Oliveira man I sell more than
el Javier oliveira tío vendo más que la
Pantoja eh I mean I wish my grandmother
Pantoja eh o sea se Ojalá mi abuela
were alive to know this eh grandma I
estuviera viva para saber esto eh abuela
sell more than Pantoja they start
vendo más que la Pantoja se ponen a
talking about me I mean they start talking about
hablar de mí o sea se ponen a hablar de
Pantoja and they are not
la Pantoja y no son
capable I will change the thumbnail I will put
capaces ya cambiaré la miniatura pondré
a picture of this boy instead of the
una foto de este muchacho en vez de la
[Laughs]
[Risas]
another God
otra Dios
kid says it the master of
chaval lo dice el maestro de los
dialogues Hey what happened between Tania and
diálogos Oye qué pasó entre Tania y
sensei that FJ is causing [ __ ]
sensei que está FJ metiendo [__] otra
again what happened between Tania and sensei doesn't
vez lo que pasó entre Tania y sensei no
interest FJ Ah okay what about Tania
le interesa a FJ Ah vale lo lo de tan
sensei neither eh let's say he says it without
sensei tampoco eh vamos que lo dice sin
getting red well it would be good if
ponerse Colorado pues estaría bueno que
Anne got red you are the pantojo of YouTube no no
Anne eres el pantojo de YouTube no no
but listen to me you the marinera eh No no
pero escúchame te la marinera eh No no
but now I've noticed like
pero ahora he notado yo como que estaba
things were a little calmer eh but it is like that
un poco más calma la cosa eh pero es así
I mean, about gossip channels man
O sea yo de de canales de salseo tío la
people usually talk about the
gente suelen hablar de los de los
streamers but not about the ones no about the
streamers pero no de los no de los
streamers who comment on gossip no I mean I
streamers que comentan salseo no O sea
don't see videos being uploaded mess
yo no veo que se suban vídeos de mess ha
said this I don't know who said said that
dicho esto no sé quién ha dich dicho lo
uncle shur said I don't know what very
otro el tío shur ha dicho no sé qué muy
strange very little mine is daily daily
raro muy poco lo mío es diario diario
but apart from that there are four four or
pero aparte que hay cuatro cuatro o
five Twitter accounts dedicated to me
cinco cuentas de Twitter dedicadas a mí
eh four or five Yes yes a few Let's
eh cuatro o cinco Sí sí unas cuantas A
see it is relevance I understand no that I do
ver es relevancia entiendo no eso
n't understand that that is repercussion and
no entiendo que eso es repercusión y
relevance  especially not many times it's not
relevancia sobre todo no muchas veces no
everything Maybe having more views is it
es todo A lo mejor tener más visitas son
may be more of the algorithm it may be
puede ser más del algoritmo puede ser
more of many of many factors
más de muchas de muchos factores
in the subject that there are people who have
en el tema de que hay gente que tiene
more views per video than me I
más visitas por vídeo que yo yo lo
attribute it to the amount of content that I
adjudico a la cantidad de contenido que
upload
subo
to that I attribute it
a eso lo adjudico
I am not calm you do not have time to
yo no está calmada no tienes tiempo de
catch up Ah well Well that will be it either
ponerte al día Ah bueno Pues será eso
I don't care to you it's like that if I
tampoco me importa te es así que si te
tell you the
digo la
truth and it wasn't between tan and sensei it was
verdad y no fue entre tan y sensei fue
something that happened and I'm not going to talk about
algo que pasó y yo no voy a hablar de
that subject that subject either eh that subject doesn't
ese tema ese tema tampoco eh ese tema no
interest us either
nos interesa tampoco
okay that subject no Javi let's see what
vale ese tema no Javi a ver qué es lo
Javi did this day they have to
que hizo Javi este día que tienen que
talk about Javi Because of course he doesn't find the
hablar de Javi Porque claro no le parece
Pantoja thing interesting he doesn't
interesante lo de la Pantoja no le
find Loli's thing interesting either and
parece interesante tampoco lo de Loli y
Peppa doesn't want to mention it and about tan
Peppa no lo quiere mencionar y lo de tan
sense he says well that
sense dice que bueno que no le importa a
nobody cares let's see what Javi has done
nadie a ver qué es lo que ha hecho Javi
nor are they interested in making a
ni le interesa a ellos que se Monte la
movie However you want to listen
película Como quiera quieres escuchar
okay
vale
Yes sir I give against the weakest because
Sí señor doy contra la más débil porque
to me if that lady donated the 240 in her
a mí si esa señora donó los 240 en su
day or she didn't do it in her day  I don't care about
día o no lo hizo en su día me da igual
the case that has made it Oh really,
el caso que lo ha hecho Ay de verdad la
people defending the 240
gente defendiendo lo de los 240
Simply because it is a lady who is let's
Simplemente porque es una señora que
say on her
está digamos en su
side I mean the the
bando O sea la la la
people who start justifying the
gente que se pone a justificar lo de los
240 lady What a shame You have to be the
240 señora Qué vergüenza Hay que ser
same as there is that just like Peppa
igual de la hay que igual que la Peppa
to defend him from the 240 and you have to
para defenderlo de los 240 y tienes que
be low low low to defend him from
ser bajo bajo bajo para defenderlo de
the 240 that not even she defends him worth it
los 240 que no lo defiende ni ella vale
she lies about the issue of the 240 the
ella miente sobre el tema de los 240 los
240 directly with a relative of a
240 directo con un familiar de una
cancer victim who was a
víctima de cáncer que era un
boy I don't remember if he was 20 something years old
chaval no me acuerdo si de 20 pico años
The boy okay takes the relative to his
El chaval vale se lleva al familiar a su
direct and to put on a medal he goes
directo y para ponerse una medalla coge
and says everything you give me today I am going to
y dice todo lo que me deis hoy lo voy a
donate for No daughter no No everything they
donar para No hija no No todo lo que te
give you no that is put an account number
den no eso se pone un número de cuenta
if you want to contribute something put the
si tú quieres aportar algo pones el
account number so they donate it there
número de cuenta para que lo donen allí
no no no donate me donate me that everything I
no no no donarme donarme que todo lo que
donated goes to
doné va para el
cancer one month two months 3 months 4 months
cáncer un mes dos meses 3 meses 4 meses
5 months 6 months  7 months 7 months and
5 meses 6 meses 7 meses 7 meses y sale
this one and the friend come out The two friends to expose
este y la amiga Los dos amigos a exponer
that she hadn't done it
que no lo había hecho ya han reconocido
she and her son have already recognized that they had forgotten So if they
ella y hijo que se les había olvidado O
don't say anything maybe they don't
sea que si no le dicen nada a lo mejor
even remember no
ni se acuerdan no
and not happy with that lion chicken Oh right
y no contenta con eso lión pollo Ay lo
away everything I don't know why she grabbed her with
ensui todo no sé porque la trincar con
the ice cream cart she
el carrito de los helados se fue
ran off in the morning a kiss mom of
corriendo por la mañana un beso mamá de
she ran off early in the morning
se fue corriendo por la mañana temprano
to the association to donate it she tried to make the
a la asociación a donarlo intentó que La
donation anonymous don't forget that she
donación fuera anónima no os olvidéis de
tried to make the donation
eso que intentó que La donación fuera
anonymous to come saying that she had
anónima para venir diciendo que lo había
done it back then And still according to
hecho en aquel entonces Y todavía según
Loli the son falsified a paper or she
Loli el hijo falsificar un papel o ella
wanted to ask the son to falsify
qu ira pedírselo al hijo que falsificar
a paper to deceive people and there
un papel para engañar a la peña y
are still people who
todavía hay gente que la
defend her like this one and like many more eh I
defiende como esta y como muchos más eh
mean the one who has the channel dedicated to me
o sea ese que me tiene el canal dedicado
defends her when they brought up the subject no he didn't
la defiende cuando le sacaron el tema no
even want to find out he's against
no quiso ni informarse está en contra de
Javi I'm not interested I collaborate with
Javi no me interesa yo colaboro con
her and he made a song with her
ella y le hizo una canción con ia
saying that she wasn't a climber let's
diciendo que no era una trepa es que
go it's that really
vamos es que de verdad
not what Mario is doing or  damn I don't want
no que va Mario ni de coña no quiero
another lawsuit because of you I
otra demanda por tu
give you permission, kidding of course they're
culpa te doy permiso di cachón claro me
suing
demandan a
me, either it's defending the 240, man, by
mí sea es que defender los 240 tío por
sides because you don't like the ones on the other
bandos porque te caen mal los del otro
side, those who fight with her, man,
bando los que se pelean con ella tío
if you don't like Jai Oliveira or you don't like
pues si te cae mal Jai oliveira o te cae
Alanne or you don't like any of the ones
mal alanne o te cae mal alguno de los
on the other side, then don't
que están en el otro bando pues no los
watch them, put on that cross stitch, go look at
veas ponte ese punto de cruz ponte a ver
Antonio David, go look at someone else, I
Antonio David ponte a ver a otro yo que
know he's into something, Alberto Mené, who
sé que está su bola Alberto mené que
's into something, but are you going to
está su bola pero te vas a poner a
support the lady with what she did with
apoyar la señora con lo que ha hecho con
the 240, for God's sake, you have no
lo de los 240 por Dios no tenéis
shame, you have no
vergüenza tenéis ninguna
shame, she did it, she did it, she did it, she did it
vergüenza lo ha hecho lo ha hecho lo ha
because her friends
hecho porque los amigos la
exposed her, there was no thought of doing it, she
expusieron no había pensamiento hacerlo
did it because her friends
lo ha hecho porque los amigos la
exposed her, she had forgotten And she
expusieron se le había olvidado Y
still wanted to cheat with the
todavía quiso engañar con el
paper, she did it when they caught her with it. The
papel lo ha hecho cuando la pillaron con
deception is unforgiving, but she did it
El engaño no perdona perona lo ha hecho
when they caught her when they caught her red-
cuando la pillaron cuando la pillaron
handed that she hadn't
con las manos en la masa que no lo había
entered it, they forced her to do it and
ingresado la obligaron a hacerlo y
then she did it, but of course this is
entonces lo hizo pero claro esto es
infamous. This is no good.  you're welcome in the lion
infame Esto no sirve de nada en el león
on the contrary it shows the need and the
al contrario demuestra la necesidad y la
scam that this lady wanted to do or
estafa que quería hacer esta señora oa
you as pol see it in another way No I
tú como pól lo ver de ot manera No yo
have to correct these two
tengo que corregir aquí a estas dos
people here he says he did it he
personas dice que lo ha hecho
says I don't think so I'm remembering that
dice no creo yo que está recordando que
the paper elito was going to show in
el papel elito que iba a enseñar en
January January passed and he already warned that he wasn't
enero pasó enero y ya avisó que no le
going to show it because he didn't feel like it he
iba a enseñar porque no le daba la
says he did it he's right
gana dice que lo ha hecho tiene razón
here the loser it's true he says he did it
aquí el pringado es verdad dice que lo
no let's see if let's see of course
ha hecho no a ver si a ver claro lo dice
she says it and We called the association
ella y Nosotros llamamos a la asociación
and they didn't confirm it of course she did it
y no lo confirmaron claro lo ha hecho ya
afterwards girl but the loser putting it
después tía pero el pringado poniéndolo
in doubt eh that she did it yet he doesn't
en duda eh que lo haya hecho todavía no
trust her of course how many things
se fía de ella ya claro cuántas cosas no
have not come out yet for the climber
habrán salido todavía para que la trepa
not to have the [ __ ] to tell this one or
no tenga [__] de conle a este ni a la
Loli TR why did you start asking him
Loli TR para qué te pusiste a pedirle
for a bottle of water for your mother
para una botella de agua para tu madre
be
ten
ashamed we're in
vergüenza estamos en
October almost a year after all this
octubre casi un año después de todo este
mess no paper has been seen nor are we
follón no se ha visto ningún papel ni lo
going to
vamos
move it nor is it going to move it is that donation
mover ni lo va mover es que esa donación
as support otherwise it would not be
como apoyo de lo contrario no sería
support It's that I believe  that if you see the
apollo Es que yo creo que si veis el
last video that Loli W made
último vídeo que ha hecho Loli W al
about it V did it because the
respecto V lo ha hecho porque la
association confirmed it but she did it the
asociación lo confirmó pero lo hizo el
day they caught her not the day they
díaa que la pillaron no el día que la
caught her but the first
pillaron sino el primer
Monday Tania also called and they gave her the
lunes Tania también llamó y le dieron la
exact same info and that she tried to
misma info exactamente y que intentó
do it anonymously she asked that
hacerlo de manera anónima le pidió que
the donation be
La donación fuera
anonymous to deceive the people who
anónima para engañar la gente que le
follow her to understand many things and the
sigue entender muchas cosas y la
importance of that and why she has no
importancia de eso y el Por qué no tiene
excuses for certain things but you only have to
excusas para ciertas cosas pero solo
watch the live that
tienes que ver el directo de que ha
Loli did from her house that is
hecho Loli desde de su casa esa que
rented by a very
tiene alquilado un extranjero muy
foreign foreigner who every time he feels like it
extranjero que cada vez que ya le da la
goes in there with his cell phone and does it
gana entrar allí con el móvil y hace
live from the room of the
directo desde la habitación del
painting But those of us who are psychologists
cuadro Pero los que somos psicólogos lo
see it very clearly eh that when someone
vemos muy claro eh que cuando alguien
wants to do t the sailor
quiere hacer t la marinería
and This is that you sent it to me Ah
y Esto va que me lo has mandado Ah que
this has nothing to do with it this is
esto no tiene nada que ver que esto es
what about the audio of the loser there is an
lo de lo del audio del pringado va un
audio of mine from WhatsApp How is it an audio of yours
audio mío de WhatsApp Cómo un audio tuyo
who says it save it for me is saying it
quién lo dice guardame lo está diciendo
now where is it wait
ahora dónde está espérate
put audio where he recognizes that she never
puesto audio dond reconoc que ella nunca
had cancer and that you don't say anything to
tuvo cáncer y que tú no dices nada para
cover it up so that she doesn't  destroy now he's
taparla para que no la destrocen ahora
going to take out the medical record Ah no
va a sacar el historial clínico Ah no
now ask yulan dic no c you will give a
ahora pregunta yulan dic no c daréis un
hair mals on the head no you do not
pelo mals en la cabeza no te no hace
need more hair there are no people who no there are
falta más pelo no hay gente que no hay
people who say that that no that no that
gente que dice que que no que no que
nobody
nadie
recognized well let's see let's see this
reconoci bueno a ver vamos a ver esto
Antonio to put you a little in
Antonio para poneros un poco en
context because Consuelo had
contexto porque Consuelo ha tenido hoy
some harsh words for David today eh I mean It
unas duras palabras para David eh o sea
turns out that Antonio David has
Resulta ser que Antonio David le ha
reproached Ortega Cano and Gloria
reprochado a Ortega Cano y a Gloria
Camila about how they have never defended
Camila sobre que nunca lo han defendido
him both but I have not seen any
él las dos pero yo no he visto ninguna
Well actually he brings the subject up
Bueno en realidad el tema lo saca para
here eh but Antonio Avilla then
aquí eh pero Antonio avilla luego lo
finishes it off public demonstration by Gloria
remata manifestación pública de Gloria
Camila in a defense of Antonio av
Camila en una defensa a Antonio av
many I you have never seen that she
muchas yo tú no has visto nunca que te
has defended you no I have never seen that she has defended me that I
haya defendido ella no yo que me haya
heard I am a good father and such [ __ ] does it
escuchado soy un buen padre y tal [__]
seem to you Are you highlighting your figure
Te parece Estás resaltando tu figura
as a father eh she is always d saying what I
como padre eh siempre d está diciendo lo
am no no no defense I don't know if I am
que soy no no ninguna defensa no sé si
explaining myself is that if she is that I
me esto explicando es que si ella es que
think that if she sees that what they are
yo creo que si ella ve que lo que están
saying is a lie she does not have to
diciendo es mentira no te tiene que
defend you she  Neither because when you are I do
defender Tampoco porque cuando tú es que
n't know how to explain it to you eh I don't believe that
no sé cómo explicarte eh yo no creo que
she I have seen her on numerous
ella yo la he visto a ella en numerosas
occasions even when she went
ocasiones incluso hasta cuando iba a su
to jail with her father and they asked him about
padre a la cárcel que le preguntaban por
his sister eh the father of my niece the
la hermana eh el padre de mi sobrina el
father of my niece and I have a very good
padre de mi sobrina y tengo muy buena
memory and I can search for those videos there is no
memoria y puedo buscar esos vídeos no
need to make a defense when you do
hace falta hacer una defensa cuando tú
not believe a person is guilty always
no crees a una persona culpable siempre
the one who has to prove things
el que tiene que que demostrar las cosas
the one who Damn but not the Def
el que [__] pero no la Def
not the one who accuses you not in this case but he
no el que te acusa no en este caso pero
has always highlighted positive things about
siempre ha resaltado cosas positivas
you and in fact let's see I think that I think
tuyas y de hecho a ver yo creo que yo
that Gloria Camila and Ortega Cano have never
creo que Gloria Camila y Ortega Cano no
come out to defend Anton av on the
han salido a defender nunca anton av del
subject because I think that in truth Gloria
tema porque yo creo que en verdad Gloria
Camila has a good relationship with Antonio
Camila tiene buena relación con Antonio
avid considers him a good father with the
avid lo considera un buen padre con el
subject of with
tema
the subject of his niece not like being
de con el tema de su sobrina no como ser
involved with his
lía con su
niece but I think that Gloria Camila and
sobrina pero yo creo que Gloria Camila y
Ortega Cano do not have 100% a good
Ortega Cano no tienen al 100% una buena
image of Antonio
imagen de Antonio
David you know remember the things that
David sabes acordaros de las cosas que
the tightwad Antonio David has said
sí ha dicho el tacano de Antonio David
So that's where I have my doubt  that it
Entonces yo ahí tengo mi duda de que
was because of that eh, there was a very good
fuera por eso eh se vio muy buena
relationship with you in Big Brother eh And in
relación contigo en gran hermano eh Y en
many debates that you two have coincided,
muchos debates que habéis coincidido los
I have seen a very good feeling and a very
dos yo he visto muy buen feeling y muy
good relationship and that she has been a girl who has
buena relación y que ha sido una chica
supported you together
que que que te ha apoyado a conjunto
when you have been on television, that is what
cuando habéis estado en televisión eso
I have perceived eh Of course, but
es lo que yo he percibido eh Claro pero
yes, let's see that our relationship is
si a ver que nuestra relación es
excellent, if I already explained it previously, I
excelente si ya lo explic anteriormente
mean, we had a conversation
o sea nosotros tuvimos una conversación
where she told me, Hey, I think this,
donde ella me dijo Oye yo pienso esto
where I told her, Hey, well, I think the
donde yo le dije Oye pues yo pienso lo
other thing and as I tell her there, I
otro y como le digo por ahí que me ha
loved it, stepped on. I mean, there's no more
encantado pasado pisado O sea no hay más
and And it's more, I mean, she's already been to my house, she's stayed
y Y es más o sea ya estado en mi casa se
overnight at my house. When
ha qued dormir en mi casa Cuando ocurrió
the pandemic happened, when I was
lo de la pandemia que yo estaba
working on Salvame, and they ended up
trabajando en salvame que terminaron
closing the hotel where we were
cerrando el hotel donde estábamos
staying, I went to Gloria's house, eh, I
hospedados yo me fui a casa de Gloria eh
mean, I want to tell you, I also have a very
o sea quiero decirte también tengo muy
good relationship with Ortega. So,
buena relación con con con Ortega O sea
fortunately, the things that we
que que afortunadamente las cosas que
had to solve were solved. And
tuvimos que solucionar se solucionaron Y
I, who am not a resentful person, so let's
yo que no soy una persona rencorosa pues
start from scratch and that's it. I
borrón cuenta nueva y ya está que me
would have liked that at the time, Yes, I  I
hubiese gustado que en su moment Sí yo
also think that or that I missed at the
también lo pienso o que ech de menos en
time a defense obviously that I
su momento una defensa obviamente que la
needed it because I probably
necesitaba pues probablemente la
needed it or probably I was not able
necesitaba o probablemente no fui capaz
to defend myself and and to put each
de defenderme solo y y de poner a cada
one in their place and obviously there is no
uno en su sitio y obviamente no hay
comparison between one and the other because
comparación entre el uno y el otro pueso
as I was saying here I have never
como decía para aquí yo jamás he
used the information that I know more
utilizado la información que conozco más
or less side in harm to attack but
o menos lado en daño para atacar sino yo
what I have always intended
lo que siempre he pretendido
is for my children to be as well as
es que mis hijos estuvieran lo mejor
possible
posible
and that the way of acting that you see it
y que la forma de actuar que lo veis
as he said is that he does not say it very
como ha dicho es que no lo dice bien
clearly the truth But you see it as
claro la verdad Pero lo veis como ha
he said that one day he had a
dicho que él en su día tuvo una
conversation I think this you think
conversación yo pienso esto tú piensas
the other there are differences his mother who
lo otro ahí hay diferencias su madre que
was spoke another thing is the cordiality that they
era habl otra cosa es la cordialidad que
have obviously because he is the father
tengan evidentemente porque es el padre
of Rocío and Gloria with Rocío you know
de Rocío y gloria con Rocío ya sabéis
How is it sometimes in magazines
Cómo es en algunas ocasiones en revistas
and other times speaking to journalists
y otras veces hablando a los periodistas
as everyone knows and putting my
como todo el mundo sabe y poniendo a mis
children in the forefront in the firing line
hijos en la palestra en el disparadero
well try to counteract
pues intentar contrarrestar
that well eh There is no more there is the
eso bueno eh No hay más ahí está la
career of one the career of the other the
carrera del uno la carrera del otro la
way of being eh Who is one Who is the
forma de ser eh Quién es uno Quién es
other and I believe that there she is the
otro y yo creo que ahí ella la partida
documentary game  Yes it's true that she didn't
documental sí que es verdad que no hizo
defend you there but I
una defensa tuya que ahí pero es que yo
think that it's that it's that it's not that she wants to
creo que es que es que no es que quiera
defend her that it's not defend her I think she
defenderla que no es defenderla yo creo
wanted to put her feet out of the water
que que quiso sacar los pies del agua
as if to say I'm leaving I'm going to drown
como diciendo me voy me voy a ahogar
up to my neck Because the sticks came to her
hasta el cuello Porque a ella le venían
for the father who was
los palos por el padre que lo ponían
also accused of being an abuser for absolutely
también de maltratador por absolutamente
everything that was said about her and I think it
todo lo que se hablaba de ella y yo creo
was like I have my
que era como en plan yo tengo Ya mi
war now I don't want to get into mach Charco
guerra no me quiero meter en mach Charco
that this is this is effectively
qu esto es esto es efectivamente
So that's where I'm going to say
Entonces ahí es donde ya voy a decir yo
the phrase that I previously omitted but
la frase que antes he obviado pero que
now I'm going to say it true because it doesn't
ahora lo voy a decir verdad porque no
only say this phrase in the video it
dice solamente en el vídeo esta
also says because who do they
frase además dice porque a quien le a
blame the reference
quien le achacan el referencia
exactly so look that's it So I mean of course of
exactamente así que mira que que ya está
course I
O sea que yo Claro que por supuesto que
respect your opinion on it was just missing I
respeto tu opinión sobre solo faltaba Yo
respect the opinion of absolutely
respeto la opinión de absolutamente todo
everyone but mine mine is that I have not
el mundo pero la mía la mía es que yo no
seen a single total where Gloria
he visto ni un solo total donde Gloria
Camila has made an express defense
Camila haya hecho una defensa expresa
when I speak because of course then
cuando yo hablo porque claro luego
we can extrapolate no no no she has done it
podemos extrapolar no no no lo ha hecho
with that affection and and now Antonio  avid I don't
con ese cariño y y ahora Antonio avid no
know if this will be the cli but I put it
sé si este será el cli pero lo he puesto
in today's news okay Yes, he
en el noticiero de hoy vale Sí que le
accuses Ortega Cano that he has
recrimina a Ortega Cano que él se ha
stuck up for him on some occasions and
daado la cara por él en alguna ocasión y
that respect that you have for each other your
ese respeto que os tenéis vuestras
opinions there has been one thing that has
opiniones ha habido una cosa que me me
made me remember this that I am going to
ha hecho recordar esto que os voy a
tell you V Yes yes That is why I say that
contar lo V Sí sí Por eso digo que que
the past is over and and and outside you did not
el pasado pisado y y y fuera no
speak, no have needed help
hablabais no de ha necesitado ha ayuda
Eh defense such I have not had but I have not
Eh defensa tal no la he tenido pero no
had it from anyone I have not needed it because I have always told the truth they have never sued me and they have blamed me for something that was not true I said that Rocío Carrasco was disloyal to me I used the term unfaithful in a
desleal utilicé el término infiel en un
court because I did not control much
juzgado porque tampoco controlaba mucho
she won in the first instance in the second
me ganó en primera instancia en segunda
instance I took it to the supreme court and
instancia lo llevé al tribunal supremo y
the supreme court ruled in my favor I
el tribunal supremo me dio la razón es
mean I have never lied and never difficult
decir jamás he mentido y nunca difícil
eh that you win that they win in the first
eh que ganes que te ganen en la primera
and in the second instance and in the
y en la segunda instancia y en el
supreme court no Uf I have been convicted for
supremo no Uf he sido condenado por
it  that's why I haven't needed
ello por eso no he necesitado defensa
any defense because the defense has been
alguna porque la defensa ha sido la
justice itself which has been the one that has
propia justicia que ha sido la que me ha
proven me right, always saying this eh there
dado la razón siempre dicho esto eh
was a detail that I remembered while
había un detalle que recordaba mientras
Now later on he starts to
Ahora más adelante se pone a
recriminate him and remind him of Ortega Cano
recriminarle y a recordarle Ortega Cano
that he I don't know if he is an enemy hti or
que él no sé si es en un enemigo hti o
something like that that he tore his clothes for
algo así que se rasgó las vestiduras por
him or something like that okay or so basically he
él o algo así vale o sea básicamente se
throws it in his face Yes the truth
lo se lo echa en cara Sí la verdad
watching on the cell phone and in one of those that
viendo en el móvil y en una de esas que
I was moving and such a live came on
que me estaba moviendo y tal me saltó un
the live also that there was about
directo el directo también que había de
Ade And I caught it almost at the end and it
de Ade Y ya lo pillé casi al final y me
surprised me because they were questioning
sorprendió porque estaban cuestionando a
Gloria Camila as if Gloria Camila
Gloria Camila como si Gloria Camila
had never stood up
nunca hubiese dado la no hubiese dado la
for Antonio David had not made
cara por Antonio David no hubiese hecho
any defense defense towards him At
ninguna defensa defensa hacia él En
that moment no and they were debating
aquel momento no y estaban debatiendo
that
eso
And then I was very surprised by what
Y entonces me sorprendió mucho lo que
he said and I say this because since he is a
dijo él y lo digo porque como es
public figure and
personaje público y se estaba hablando
his cause was being talked about I am going to say it has nothing to
de su causa lo voy a decir no tiene nada
do with the channel or with stories
que ver con el canal ni con historias
okay news, I mean I am surprised by the
vale noticia o sea me sorprende el
headline of I don't need a
titular de yo no necesito
defense because the one who has
defensa porque a mí quien me ha
defended me has been  justice is what has
defendido ha sido la justicia que es la
ruled in my favor and I say look, well it
que me ha dado la razón y digo Mira pues
's true because my support for him
es verdad porque yo mi apoyo hacia él
was believing in justice which is what
fue creyendo en la justicia que es la
has ruled in his favor but of course
que le ha dado la razón a él pero claro
if Antonio David doesn't need a
si Antonio David no necesita
defense Consuelo with your eyes and your
defensa Consuelo con tus ojos y tu
husband you can already boast of your power Oh thank you
marido ya puedes presumir de poderío Ay
very much if you go around bragging that you
Muchas gracias si tú vas presumiendo de
don't need a
que no necesitas
defense because the one who has
defensa porque a ti quien te ha
defended you has been justice and that's
defendido ha sido la justicia y así es
true From now on
de verdad A partir de ahora
eh From now on that against
eh A partir de ahora eso de contra las
injustices m blue we have to defend
injusticias m azul hay que defender a
Antonio David What value do you give him because you have
Antonio David Qué valor le das porque
thrown the value of that defense to
has tirado el valor de esa defensa por
the
los
ground words of yesterday you have left that
suelos palabras de ayer has dejado esa
defense thrown by slabs when I
defensa tirada por losos yo cuando
heard eh I don't need any
escuché eh yo no necesito ninguna
defense because justice has defended me
defensa porque a mí me ha defendido la
making
justicia haciendo
reference making reference that
referencia haciendo referencia que
Gloria Camila publicly never
Gloria Camila públicamente nunca lo
defended him And that is what they were
defendió Y eso es lo que estaban
questioning I am dead
cuestionando me quedo muerta
when I don't need a defense because the one
cuando yo no necesito defensa porque a
who has defended me has
mí quien me ha defendido han sido ha
been
sido la
justice
justicia
Bravo you have left
Bravo has dejado sin
Gloria Camila without e He had no reason to
e Gloria Camila No tenía por qué
defend anything She has always said that
defender nada Ella siempre ha dicho que
he is a very good father that he is the father of
él es muy buen padre que es el padre de
her  niece and that he is a very good father
su sobrina y que es muy buen padre
eh but of course if I that is that argument
eh pero claro si yo esa es ese argumento
that you have to say that you have not
que tienes para decir que tú no has
needed a public defense because the one who
necesitado defensa pública porque a ti
has defended you has been
quien te ha defendido ha sido la
justice giving you the reason Sorry for the I
justicia dándote la razón Perdona el yo
rebel and the blue sea what is it for if
me revelo y la mare azul para qué es si
you do not need it because
tú no lo necesitas porque a ti ya te
justice already defends you
defiende la justicia
Explain it to me I still don't, I
A mí que me lo expliquen Yo todavía no
mean I have not prosecuted him I mean he has
lo o sea yo no lo he procesado digo es
left all those people without weapons
que ha dejado sin armas a todas esas
with those statements all
personas con esas declaraciones a todas
those people who break their faces for
esas personas que se parten la cara por
him on YouTube in the spaces and
él en YouTube en los espacios y en todos
everywhere let them look at it let them
sitios que se lo hagan mirar que se lo
look at it he is right because the one
hagan mirar que lleva razón porque a él
who has defended him has been
quien lo ha defendido ha sido la
justice which is what I have always
justicia que es lo que yo siempre he
said I mean once I stopped
dicho o sea yo una vez deje de
questioning that network
cuestionar a esa cadena
well anyway nonsense I
bueno en fin
also tell you eh nonsense
chorradas también te digo eh chorradas
Hey racel today we don't have a video or
Oye racel hoy no tenemos vídeo o
what yes we have a video we have a video we have a
qué sí tenemos
video but there is another one here I mean we have
vídeo pero es que hay otro aquí
this one and we have another one
o sea tenemos este y tenemos
we have two videos We watch them or
otro tenemos dos vídeos Los vemos o
what every time you come home you catch them in
qué siempre que vuelves a casa pillas en
the
la
kitchen Oh but this one is Loli from
cocina Ah pero que está es Loli de
true I mean but what does he do what does he do
verdad O sea pero que hace que hace
straight here to the Arguiñano
directo aquí a los arguiñano
now with his hands in
ahora de con las manos en
Well the water has fallen on me eh man who hasn't
Pues me ha caído el agua eh tío que no
shown up to the lawsuit
se ha presentado a la demanda
eh who hasn't shown up the
eh que no se ha presentado la
lawsuit he had 20 days to respond to
demanda tenía 20 días para responder a
the lawsuit and they have given us the date of
la demanda y nos han dado fecha del de
the hearing
la vista de la audiencia
without that he is not going to
sin que no se va a
show up that he doesn't feel like it
presentar que no le ha da la gana
I am amazed at
yo alismo alucino con el pasotismo de la
people's apathy regarding these issues man I am amazed
gente respecto a esos temas tío alucino
[Music]
[Música]
eh one of the bathroom and I put it here because
eh una del baño y lo pongo aquí porque
if not I am going to watch the TR of the
si no voy a poner a ver la TR de la
[Music]
[Música]
beach I am going to put
playa voy a poner
here the water that was thrown like this but
aquí el agua que tirado así
when a pap
per cuando un pap
[Music]
[Música]
already here now what have I done with the paper
ya aquí ahora qué he hecho con el papel
removed the paper removed the
quit el papel quit
paper
papel
disappeared do you remember that there was a
desapareció os acordáis que había un
plate around
plato por
here the Listen
aquí la Escuchar
Loli let's see I was going to ask I put no
Loli a ver iba a preguntar yo Pon no
olive oil I tend to put a little
oliva le tend poner un poquito de aceite
olive oil or something no Although I don't know Nothing
de oliva o algo no Aunque no se te Nada
here until today I don't know It's nothing
aquí hasta hoy no lo sé No pasa nada
cauliflower Look
coliflor Mirad
eh I pick it up like it was the dove it's
eh lo cojo como si fuera la paloma está
super  cooked Okay cda let's see
super cocida Está bien cda a ver la
let's put
ponemos
it on now I guess what we have to
aleale ahora Supongo yo que lo que hay
do is put in some lach no
que hacer será echarle lach no
[Music]
[Música]
gamel lor Hello
gamel lor Hola
bechamel I haven't put in time I got
bechamel que no le puesto tiempo me he
excited I got
emocionado me he
[Music]
[Música]
excited I left little time eh I'm
emocionado dej poco tiempo eh
going are you scared do you think
voy está usted asustado cree que le
something might happen to him yes yes yes that I'm
puede pasar algo sí sí sí que me quedo
going to run out com come on let's get
sin com venga vamos a sacar
this
estoo
body out this is a cooking video I
cuerpo est es un vdeo de cocina Yo
want some sauce Okay okay To me
quiero un salseo Bueno está bien A mí me
mom I like the thing is that
mamá a mí es que me gusta el rollito est
people come in you tell us your opinion
de que entren la gente digas su opinión
and all this if I like it and if someone comes in
y todo esto si me gusta y si entra
for you I'm not going to say anything
alguien para ti ya no te digo nada
are you listening Yeah yeah yeah Okay
estáis escuchando Sí sí sí Bueno pues
now I'm listening to you
ahora te estoy escuchando ya a ti
perfectly without an earpiece and I have
perfectamente sin pinganillo y tengo
my people here in the okay you don't
aquí a mi gente en el vale tú no
hear us on your cell phone No I'm
escuchas a nosotros por el móvil No yo
listening to you on your cell phone
estoy escuchando a ustedes por el móvil
okay listen well I can't hear
vale escucha bien no escucho
perfectly we're finishing people ha
perfectamente vamos terminando gente ha
okay okay the space the space howy
bien está bien el space el space comoy
the space is that he doesn't LL F space you dude
el space es que no le LL F space tí tío
makes a space has made a space and what
hace un space ha hecho un space y lo que
The gindy comes up with Well of course if they've
se le ocurre El gindy Bueno claro si le
named it something of mine no
han puesto de título algo mío no
space the space like the space that isn't
space el space como el space que no le
called space calls it
llama espacio le llama
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
space I'm cracking up and I'm splitting my
space me parto y me
sides And that's what they've done
mondo Y eso eso es lo que han hecho
today tremendously pathetic eh
hoy tremendamente patético eh
tremendously pathetic guys I'm going to the let's
tremendamente patético chicos me voy
see I'm going to do a raid and I'm
para la a ver voy a hacer una raide y me
going to the salsería if anyone wants to
voy para la salsería si alguien quiere
go there well let them go
ir para allá bueno que se vaya
No I don't know who dreams about you more if I
No no sé quién sueña más contigo si
choose the mother
elijo la madre
eh What thing What thing What thing What thing
eh Qué cosa Qué cosa Qué cosa Qué cosa
my [ __ ] My God inter let's go there for
me cao Dios mío inter vámonos para allá
a while come on go I'm going
un rato venga
there okay Hey by the way if you do
va voy para allá vale Oye por cierto si
n't want to go to the salsería we
no queréis ir para la salsería también
've also uploaded a newscast Here between
hemos subido un noticiero Aquí entre
gossip okay you're free enjoy the
salseo vale sois libres disfrutad del
content and have a good
contenido y que paséis buen fin de
weekend okay Anyway even if I don't
semana vale De todas maneras aunque no
do it live during the weekend we'll
haga directo durante el fin de semana
see each other on Sunday with Marina esnal
nos veremos el domingo con Marina esnal
Okay and I think with a pretty
Ok y creo que con un invitado bastante
important guest also quite powerful Okay you
importante también bastante potente Ok
have a newscast video Here that
tenéis vídeo de noticiero Aquí que lo
we uploaded while we were
hemos subido mientras que estábamos en
live we're going to the salsería and on the
directo vamos para la salsería y en el
main channel  You have the chat with
canal principal tenéis la charla con
Pedro García, okay,
Pedro García guado
kisses, handsome,
vale besos guapísimo
kisses, I'm going over there to the salsería,
besos me voy para allá para la salsería
okay, go over there
vale tirar para allá
[Music]
[Música]